An all -new 2020 starts
right now.
Family secrets are spilling out.
I need my daddy.
A teenager with a strange
demeanor.
She's clutching a teddy bear.
How can she be actually
18 years of age?
And an even stranger story
about her missing mother.
I didn't know Bonnie was
going to go missing.
Something happened to her.
She didn't just disappear on
her own free will.
So you knew something was
really wrong.
No. Pretty much.
Has she ever disappeared before?
No.
Whoever has my sister, please
let her go.
Maybe somebody saw her somewhere
at a bus station, at
a train station, in a
cab, at the mall.
Nathan, you can agree to
walk us through a few
areas.
We're running out of time.
He said at times, I
feel like I have the
devil living inside me.
Turns out, Bonnie wasn't the
only missing person in that
household.
Police at Alton need the
public's help finding a missing
woman.
Bonnie Woodward was last seen.
It's a missing person's case
that will confound an Illinois
community.
I didn't see any...
Flooding, seasoned investigators with no
shortage of witnesses.
And then possibly tried to
get rid of her.
These interviews happening in this
room right here.
Focusing on one person, one
mother of four,
whose sudden and perplexing disappearance
sets off alarm bells.
It all started at the
end of a day's shift
one afternoon in June.
Bonnie Woodward got off around
3pm.
That day, she was working
at what was called a
Unismith nursing home here in
Alton.
It was a normal day
of work for her.
47 years old, worked at
the nursing home for over
25 years, I believe.
And just a woman who
was reliable.
Being a nurse's aide is,
that's a lot of caregiving.
She had it forever.
She loved what she did.
She went to work, she
worked her shift, and then
would come home to her
children every night.
As well as...
Gary Wilmorth, who she was
dating at the time.
Gary knew that she had
some sort of staff meeting
after work from 2 to
3.
So he really wasn't expecting
her home until, you know,
3 .34.
That boyfriend, Gary Wilmorth, says
he tries getting a hold
of Bonnie around 4 o
'clock.
But his call goes straight
to voicemail.
Your call has been forwarded
to an automatic voice message
system.
Everybody was like, she would
call if she was five
minutes away.
Oh no, she was, everything
she did was on a
schedule.
Nobody had seen her.
This was very abnormal for
Bonnie.
She was always in communication
with her family.
After she didn't return home,
her family members, they reached
out.
They tried to call her,
they tried to text her,
and no response.
And by the next morning,
when Bonnie doesn't show up
for work,
her co -workers are alarmed
by something they see in
the parking lot.
Her red Chevy Avalanche was
still parked at the nursing
home, had not moved from
the previous date.
The windows had been down,
even during the overnight hours.
She loved that truck.
She worked really hard to
get that truck.
She absolutely loved it.
So she wouldn't have just
left it.
At that point, it was
clear that there was something
wrong.
And Gary reported her disappearance
to our department the morning
of the 26th.
When we work on the
missing person and we're dealing
with an adult,
you have to keep in
mind the possibility if they
just want to take a
break.
They want to get away
from family and friends.
And that's natural.
Also, I have to look
into what's usual and what's
their history.
Detectives assigned to the case
soon learn that 47 -year
-old Bonnie Woodward is a
force of nature.
Bonnie survived breast cancer.
She was a fierce mother
to four children.
Bonnie has two grown children
from her first marriage.
Joseph, who's 28, and Jennifer,
26.
Bonnie is also mom to
two stepkids, Heather and Aaron.
She adopted them after their
father, Bonnie's third husband, passed
away.
Heather was about 17 years
old at this time.
And Aaron was special needs,
and she cared for him
every day.
Bonnie is also a devoted
grandmother.
She grew up as one
of nine siblings, so she
has a large extended family.
What kind of aunt was
she?
She was the aunt that
took a second to actually
listen to you if something
was going on.
And she had a big
personality.
Oh, yeah, no, huge personality.
Very loving.
Her house is where a
lot of the cousins all
congregated.
She had this little case
in her living room, and
she'd have little figurines and
random stuff that had dolphins
on it.
None of it made sense
to me, but she loved
them.
So she was the social
hub.
Kind of, yeah.
She kind of liked having
everybody around.
So you knew something was
really wrong.
Pretty much.
With the clock ticking,
the Auden detectives start their
missing person investigation where you'd
expect,
at the last place she
was reportedly seen.
This is where Bonnie worked?
Yes, this Unismith nursing home.
And she was a very
consistent employee.
Yes, didn't miss any work
at all, and certainly wouldn't
miss without calling in.
And so where was her
car parked?
It was in the spots
here.
And the windows were rolled
down?
Yeah, windows were rolled down.
So you would have to
imagine that she expected to
come back to the hospital.
Yeah.
Back here, presumably, no surveillance
was captured.
No.
At that time, there was
no surveillance back here that
we could rely on.
Without any surveillance footage, officers
are hopeful that Bonnie's car
may actually give them some
clues as to what may
or may not have happened.
The vehicle, there's no significant
damage to it or anything
like that that would cause
us any alarm.
And upon looking at the
inside, there was no evidence
of a struggle.
So we ended up having
this vehicle towed to our
police department, secured, until we
could process it, and also
dust it for prints.
One of the early things
was how Bonnie Woodward was
really regular with cashing her
paycheck.
The day she disappeared was
payday, and she would, every
time she was paid on
Fridays, she would take that
check to the bank.
That was a ritual?
Ritual.
The check never got cash,
she never went to the
bank.
Nothing happened with any of
her phone, social media.
Bank accounts all went dead
as of 4 p .m.
that day.
And so then we have
to look at what other
troubles that she may have
in her life.
We have to look at
prior relationships.
Gary Wilmarth, her current boyfriend.
And so what did you
find when you dug into
Gary's background?
Gary's got a colorful past.
He's a convicted felon, and
they've had some domestic issues.
And just for the record,
sir, what is your name,
your full name?
Gary.
J -A -R -Y.
Okay.
Wilmarth, W -I -L -M
-U -R -T -H.
Bonnie was the love of
my life, and she was
a good -hearted woman.
And, I mean, she put
up with me, and, I
mean, that wasn't easy.
When Gary's talking to police,
he tells them that they've
been an on -and -off
couple for about seven years.
Everything good over the past
ten months between you two?
Yeah.
Ever any arguments or fights
or plastics?
No, just a little money
problem, you know, because construction's
slow.
Right.
But we've been working it
out.
I mean, I'm not a
good boy.
I mean, I've had a
record myself in the past.
I've paid my time, and
Bonnie knew that.
Bonnie still loved me.
She didn't care what I
did in my past.
And, uh, these cops sure
did.
Have you heard anything from
her at all since then?
Nothing.
Bonnie's daughter, Jennifer, alibied him
at home.
And Gary was waiting for
her to get home because...
She said they were both
there the whole day together.
And, ultimately, he did end
up doing a polygraph examination
and passed it.
But as investigators start talking
to Bonnie's coworkers,
they learn she was last
seen getting into a strange
car
with an unknown man.
I guess I had never
seen the man before.
The police wondered, could Bonnie
be having an affair?
Or was it something worse?
Nothing is out of the
realm of possibility.
How did she know this
person?
I mean, Mom had to
have known the person she
got into the car with.