Roger Carroll pleads not guilty
to the murder of Bonnie
Woodward, but he's facing some
tall odds.
He may just not understand
how tall.
One of the key pieces
of evidence turned out to
be a sassafras tree.
Yes.
Tell me how you decided
that you were going to
try to bring that into
the courtroom.
I'll be honest, we didn't
decide it. It was kind
of thrust upon us by
an investigator in Jersey County.
And all of us were
kind of like, yeah, go
ahead, whatever.
It isn't every day a
tree becomes a star witness
in a murder trial.
But this was never your
ordinary, everyday case.
So how would it factor
in?
Well, that and over a
hundred other key pieces of
evidence are finally being presented
in court.
Nearly a decade after Bonnie
Woodward went missing.
I thought everybody would give
up. I mean, I didn't
know what else to do.
And him being...
Being charged with Bonnie's murder
gave me life again.
And I thought, let's do
it.
The why question is very
difficult in this case because
there's not a clear -cut
motive.
Given what you were up
against, the fact that you
didn't have a body, you
didn't really have a motive,
you didn't have a weapon,
how confident were you that
you could get a guilty
verdict?
My partner and I said
this is just never going
to get any better.
We have everything we're ever
going to get, so we
thought we'd swing the bat.
In my years as a
prosecutor, I did five cases
where the victim's body wasn't
found, and it's a gamble.
So sometimes what you'll do
in lieu of that is
you have the person declared
dead.
It can, depending on the
case, really help the jury.
We took note that now
had been eight years that
Bonnie had not been seen.
So one of the first
steps we had to take
was to have Bonnie officially
declared deceased and were able
to obtain a death certificate
based on the circumstantial evidence
that she had not been
seen.
My name is Jennifer Schock,
and I was juror number
two.
What had you heard about
the case?
I hadn't. I truly came
in there not knowing anything
prior.
And when you realized how
big a case you were
deliberating on, what was your
reaction?
A little nervous to have
that much pressure put on
me to basically decide somebody's
future.
In opening statements, the prosecution
detailed what they say happened
during Bonnie's kidnapping,
including the fact that Roger
Carroll's fingerprints were found on
her car.
They also brought in Roger
Carroll's suicide attempt.
The jury must decide if
Roger is guilty of first
-degree murder.
The earlier charges against him
and Monica for harboring a
runaway, Heather, would be dismissed.
The defense opened up by
vowing to poke holes in
the state's case, particularly taking
aim at the son, Nathan
Carroll,
telling the jury his story
changed only after being granted
immunity.
Or what they called a
golden ticket.
Nathan was on the stand
for a good two to
three hours, maybe more.
I mean, just like in
the grand jury, you could
hear a pin drop in
that courtroom while he's testifying.
Because family secrets are spilling
out in this courtroom.
I mean, he's telling a
cold, hard, disgusting story that
clearly there was no doubt
that was truthful.
Nathan testifies that he heard
gunshots and told the jury
in gruesome detail
how he helped her.
And how he helped his
father burn Bonnie's body.
I think Nathan realizes that
his dad tried to kill
his mom, and that's just
crossing the line.
If you think about Nathan,
he is a young child.
And he's being controlled by
dad, and he witnesses something
horrific.
The son, Nathan, testifies.
And I'm told that it
was a very stirring, powerful
testimony.
What do you remember of
it?
I remember that after Nathan
testified,
it was completely silent.
It was just a silence
through the whole entire courtroom
afterwards.
It was just a silence
through the whole entire courtroom
afterwards.
Nathan's testimony doesn't really make
sense.
Nathan keeps saying he's reluctant,
he did it anyway.
Why would Nathan help his
father do it?
What's in it for him?
It's a big mystery.
Nathan can be hard to
read.
He was ashamed.
He knew what he had
done was wrong.
He knew what his father
had done was wrong.
And he knew that helping
clean up was wrong.
He was very remorseful.
A lot of the trial
was built around corroborating what
he was telling us was
the truth.
We didn't want the jury
to just have to take
Nathan's word for it.
We didn't want the jury
to just have to take
Nathan's word for it.
We wanted to show that
it fit and matched all
the forensic evidence in this
case.
But the defense just keeps
chipping away at that evidence,
including those 27 bone fragments
that were found on the
property.
including those 27 bone fragments
that were found on the
property.
Bones were found, but they're
not the bones of the
deceased.
Bones were found, but they're
not the bones of the
deceased.
We were never actually able
to find DNA of Bonnie
Woodward on these bone fragments.
We were never actually able
to find DNA of Bonnie
Woodward on these bone fragments.
We were able to say
that these were bone fragments
believed to be of human
origin,
We were able to say
that these were bone fragments
believed to be of human
origin,
but we could not definitively
say that they were Bonnie
Woodward's.
but we could not definitively
say that they were Bonnie
Woodward's.
In fact, it's not clear
if they're human bones or
animal bones,
In fact, it's not clear
if they're human bones or
animal bones,
or whether they're bones that
were from an Indian burial
many years ago.
Prosecutors argued that the bones
were degraded by the fire,
which Nathan described that burned
Bonnie's body.
And to prove that there
actually was a fire on
the property,
the prosecution used an unexpected
method and witness.
Nathan identified the burn spot
on this ridge behind the
house.
Nathan identified the burn spot
on this ridge behind the
house.
And where the burn spot
was is a sassafras tree.
The sassafras tree has a
scarred spot on the bark
several feet up the tree.
The sassafras tree has a
scarred spot on the bark
several feet up the tree.
The sassafras tree has a
scarred spot on the bark
several feet up the tree.
The sassafras tree has a
scarred spot on the bark
several feet up the tree.