He cut slices out of
the tree. We sent him
off to a botanist. He
examined the tree, its age,
its growth rings, and said
that tree was damaged in
the early growing season of
2010, spring or summer.
That tree damage, according to
the testimony of a botanist
from the University of Wisconsin,
was reminiscent of a fire
and appears to have happened
at the same time Nathan
claimed Bonnie's body had been
burned.
As a prosecutor, why is
that critical?
That fire, others have testified,
had to be quite large
to burn a body like
that down to the fragments
that we found.
There's a question, was there
actually evidence of a fire?
Or is it a fire
around the time of 2010?
Or is it not a
fire? That's questionable.
Heather Woodward, Bonnie's stepdaughter, takes
the stand and tells jurors
that she told Roger about
Bonnie's whereabouts and her work
schedule.
How did Heather do on
the stand? What was her
testimony like?
It was pretty short, and
I think the way that
Heather was in the police
interviews is the way she
was on the stand.
I never wanted that to
happen to Bonnie. I mean,
sometimes I knew how she
was being, but I wouldn't
do that to her.
Her testimony, it pretty much
tracked with that, but it
was clear to those involved
that she had not participated
in her mother's death.
What made her cry on
the stand, do you remember?
Every time she cried, it
was because she said, I
never wanted this to happen
to Bonnie. I never meant
for this to happen to
Bonnie.
Bonnie's boyfriend, Gary, took to
the stand, too, and told
the jury about what was
lost when Bonnie's life was
cut short.
He wouldn't look back at
me for nothing. I kept
looking across where he was,
and he wouldn't look at
me.
So I started talking to
the jury to my right,
and I said he took
away a good woman, mother.
I let him know what
kind of person he was.
I have an old supervisor.
Before I started my very
first body case, which I'll
never forget, he said,
always remember, the jury can
see the soul of your
victim reflected in the eyes
of those who love them.
When it was their turn,
the defense team laid out
a case that pointed the
finger at Nathan as Bonnie's
killer,
and argued that without him
and the so -called golden
ticket, the state's case was
just circumstantial.
Nathan didn't have a choice.
Nathan didn't help his father
dispose.
Of this crime, Nathan's a
dead man. And let's not
forget, he was a barely
16 -year -old boy.
Roger did not testify at
trial. It's his choice whether
or not to testify, and
he decided not to.
He was advised not to
testify. Many attorneys advise their
clients not to testify,
because, one thing, they think
it will shift the burden.
They think the jury's going
to look at whether they
believe the defendant,
and suddenly the defendant has
to prove his innocence, which
he normally doesn't have to
do.
After five days...
The case is now in
the hands of the jury.
It was back and forth,
all the way.
Those moments are always very
tense.
We would get close, and
then somebody would say something
else, and then it would
throw everything off.
What was the hang -up
then?
The cases have been presented,
and now the verdict is
in the hands of the
jury.
It was back and forth,
all the way, truly, till
the end. We were back
and forth.
And we thought we would
get close, and then somebody
would say something else,
and then it would throw
everything off.
What was the hang -up
then?
We all agreed that he
definitely had a hand in
this.
The hang -up was, basically,
did he do it, or
was he covering for someone
else that did it?
When you finally reached a
decision, what was the feeling
in the room? Relief?
We truly did our due
diligence on deliberating correctly.
We were notified that the
jury had a verdict, so
we all went back to
the courtroom,
and those moments are always
very tense.
Roger Carroll was found guilty
of first -degree murder.
And so when the verdict
was read, how did the
courtroom respond?
Crying from both sides, happy
on Bonnie's side, sad on
Roger's side,
and, again, Roger never, he
never made any emotion. He
just sat there.
He didn't even react?
Mm -mm.
What went through your mind
when you heard the verdict?
Bonnie.
Um, that finally she could
be at peace.
That she could rest.
Um, I don't believe in
the word closure. It doesn't
exist in my mind.
Um, but that Bonnie can
now rest peacefully.
By the time of sentencing,
the charges against Roger for
domestic violence and obstruction were
dropped.
At the sentencing hearing, Roger
was given the opportunity to
make a statement to the
court,
and he chose to use
that time to be defiant.
He said, I don't have
anything to be sorry for.
I won't apologize because I've
done nothing wrong.
And that says a lot
about his mindset.
Sure does.
When I heard the jury
found him guilty, that was
a blessing to my ears
to hear.
Wish he could have got
more time than he did.
He was charged with first
-degree murder, um, while using
a firearm.
He received 40 years in
the Department of Corrections for
the murder, plus 25 years
for the gun enhancement.
At least it did lock
him up.
I give him that.
The police finally making him
pay for what he did.
Roger Carroll robbed her kids,
her grandkids, friends, family.
But we won't never forget
her.
And we won't forget him.
People describe her as somebody
who had a really loving
heart.
I know, she definitely did.
Like, even, especially with family,
like, didn't matter what you
did.
She would figure out a
way to,
just make it better.
You really loved her.
Oh, yeah. Like, she was
great.
Sometimes I'll look up at
the sky and tell her
I don't know if I'll
be there, but, uh, I
hope someday I will.
And see you again.
So many of Bonnie's loved
ones wishing they could see
her again.
Bonnie Woodward's killer, Roger Carroll,
is appealing his conviction.
He was granted permission for
that appeal by the Illinois
Supreme Court.
And his case will likely
be argued this fall.
That's our program for tonight.
Thanks for watching.
I'm Deborah Roberts.
And I'm David Muir from
all of us here at
20 -20 and ABC News.
Good night.