The violence in this town
is out of control.
Somebody is going to jail.
Careful.
St. Paul Police!
See the bullet hole?
It's the cops! Open the
door!
Come in, come in, come
in!
Hurry, come on, come on,
hurry, come on, come on!
She's...
She's what?
Unresponsive.
She's right here.
I had this dream already
of this.
I know what you guys
was gonna do to me,
sir.
I knew it already, man.
I knew it already.
What's happening there?
Where's the suspect?
What is your name, please?
Okay, you need to talk
to a medical...
You need to talk to
a medical dispatcher.
Hold on one, please.
Okay, get them here now.
I will... I will...
Okay, we're sending...
We're sending calls right now.
What part of the body
was she shot?
Just hurry up!
Is she awake?
Listen to me.
We've got help coming right
now, okay?
Okay, hurry up!
Are you next to her
that you can start CPR?
No!
Or if you can help
her.
Then don't do that, okay?
Careful.
St. Paul Police!
See the bullet hole?
It's the cops!
Open the door!
Police!
Come in, come in!
St. Paul Police!
Hurry!
Don't come!
Police!
She's...
She's really...
Here.
Just come to the parking
lot.
Don't let them come out.
She goes right underground.
We'll just need one medic
to come out.
Shut the door.
Yeah, let's see that.
Just one.
Watch where you're stepping.
Here, one victim's right here.
One victim.
She's got a wound right
under the eye.
We only have one?
Yeah, it's just one.
Just one.
Oh, through the door.
You could just stay out.
Because, like, he has to
just...
Alright.
You know what I'm saying?
Okay.
Um, she's right here.
She was unresponsive when we
arrived.
She what?
Unresponsive.
Yeah.
She's, like, right here.
She was unresponsive when we
arrived.
She passed away?
She's pretty...
I mean, she...
It's traumatic.
It's a traumatic arrest.
Whatever you guys want to
do.
Oh, we're done.
I mean, she is...
It's...
It's a bullet hole, right?
Right.
It's a traumatic arrest.
She has a PA of
about 30.
Yeah.
We're just calling it.
Okay.
I mean, they got the...
The black girl probably pulled
through a window.
It just...
Maybe she pulled it to
lock it.
I will work on getting
you a name.
Alright.
Just being tight for you.
Okay.
So, um...
We asked who was it.
They didn't say nothing.
What did you guys see?
White GMT.
I swear to God.
White GMT?
Yes.
Did you see who shot?
White GMT truck?
Newer?
Older?
Hold on.
Just stay...
I'm sorry.
Just stay here.
Okay.
Who?
365.
You're lying.
Hard to say.
Suspects came in a white
GMT truck.
Just say that.
I just said that.
Oh, my God.
Did you see who the
shooter was?
We...
We went in here...
Yeah.
...a few days ago.
What's his name?
And my brother friend, he
had died in an incident.
And that was his dad
that just came and shot
my mom.
His dad?
What was his name?
You know?
His name is Terrell Johnson.
That's his name?
Terrell Darrell Johnson.
And did you see him?
What?
Did you see him?
No.
We didn't see him.
Why do you think it's
him?
Because...
Because I know his truck.
Because his truck.
I know his truck.
Okay.
I know.
I swear I know.
I'm not going...
I know.
How old is this?
How old is Terrell?
We don't know.
Okay.
Well, this is what...
What did you guys see
and hear?
This is...
We didn't see or hear
anything.
Nothing?
Were you guys here?
Yes.
Okay.
We was just up there
playing board games.
Okay.
We were playing board games.
Yeah.
And somebody knocked on her
door.
She went to go see
who it was and they
shot her.
Okay.
Which way did it go?
This way.
The car was parked this
way.
Yeah.
And then what?
That way towards Bain?
Yes.
This way.
I can't see past the
stop sign.
Okay.
Is the house clear?
Yes.
The house is clear.
I haven't gone back there
yet.
Have you guys?
Terrell Dunn.
Terrell.
After G .J. got shot.
Yes.
Everybody's numbers.
Oh my God.
What was the last time
you guys saw her?
I haven't seen her at
all.
Oh my God.
G .J.
I can't see her.