My partner is going to
kind of talk to you
about what you're doing.
Do you have any idea
what you're doing here?
I do.
Tell me about that.
So, my kid gets shots
in the face.
What's his name?
Terrell Johnson, man.
Okay.
So, my kid gets shot
in the face.
The guy that shot him,
his mother, gets injured or
whatever,
and the kid said to
my kid's mother,
well, it might be your
dad that killed my mom.
I'm not killing nobody, man.
My son got shot, man.
That's it, man.
My son got shot.
That's it.
I just ride past.
They know that.
Man, they know how I
look and everything, man.
They know how I look.
They asked that lady,
hey, how do your baby
daddy look?
They know how I look.
Tell me about when you
said you ride past.
What does that mean?
Since my sons got shot,
I ride past, and I
go see.
I asked that they told
me and my kid's mother.
They didn't want to tell
us a story about what
happened to my kid.
We don't feel like talking
right now.
And I say, okay, well,
I'll come to you, and
I'll ride past every day.
I mean, we cool.
I'm like, you guys, it's
dad as well.
Why wouldn't you want to
talk to me?
That's it.
You guys have known each
other a long time.
Yeah.
They played on my son's
basketball team for seven years,
man.
Okay.
That's a chunk.
Yeah.
It's kind of weird that
I'm here.
I read the signs and
stuff, and I'm like, this
is some stuff, man, pertaining
to kids, man.
That ain't my lifestyle.
You understand me?
This is not right to
me.
This isn't the first time
that this has happened over
here.
Right?
My son's been shot once
before in McDonough Projects from
her house.
Okay.
Right.
Their house gets shot up
in Mount Airy.
Oh, I'm telling my son
every time, why would you
hang with somebody that has
brothers?
You don't hang with three
brothers, son.
He's three friends and a
stranger.
He don't get it until
this happens to him.
He gets shot in the
face.
It hurt my heart to
death.
It hurt me and my
family.
But I'm not doing nothing
with no lady, my man.
I'm an adult.
If I'm going to do
something, it's going to be
the dude that did something
to my child.
I still feel that same
way.
I want him to die
before me.
I want that.
Yeah.
He hurt my child.
But I'm not going to
hurt him.
I'm not going to hurt
nobody, man.
So I don't need to
be at homicide.
Right.
You said you just drive
by then.
I drive.
Have you tried to make
contact with them there?
Yes, we have.
Okay.
We got text messages and
everything, man.
Tell me about that.
We text them and ask
them the story.
Who is them?
Mari.
Mari is the oldest son.
Okay.
She has like three boys.
And they're all the same
age group as my son.
Okay.
If you go on Facebook,
this is what they said.
They said.
So we didn't know a
story.
Okay.
My son is, he was
so messed up that he
couldn't talk for a while.
So he couldn't say a
story or he couldn't do
anything.
And I'm not with his
mother.
And when I go down
there, they didn't let me
in because.
Down in the hospital?
Yeah.
Okay.
Her other, her boyfriend is
there, but her husband, you
know, because they've been together
for about six years.
But they didn't let me
in.
Whatever.
I sat down there, me
and the guy get into
an altercation.
The husband?
Yeah.
Okay.
And I go on Facebook.
I'm angry.
I'm upset.
I say her name on
the thing and everything.
I say his name as
well.
The next day, she contacts
my mother and me and
her are talking without him.
And she's telling me how
she talked to him and
stuff.
And then I'm telling her.
Well, I ride past there
all the time and I
see the little dudes standing
out there and you know,
I mean, I, I, you
know, I asked them and
they told me the same
thing, right?
I'm like, they're going to
talk.
He's going to actually just
wait till JJ come around.
When JJ came around, um,
the little guys, they keep
texting them and stuff.
Right.
And like, um, trying to
give him a story because
Jarrell was supposed to be.
Unconscious or something to where
he didn't know what happened.
So they're trying to give
him a story.
Okay.
He says the lady come
in and she keeps saying,
is you going to tell
him my son or something
or, um, giving him the
story?
And she said, I'm going
to tell the police that
you came here.
Don't tell him that you
got shot here or something.
He was saying, right.
When you say the lady,
who are you talking about?
I don't know.
You said the lady is
telling him.
The lady, he said, it's
a lady.
It's a, it's a dog
at the house as well.
So she's telling him that,
um, don't tell the cops
that he got shot here.
There at that house.
Exactly.
That's it.
That's all we knew.
That's the only story he
said.
And I said, well, and
like I told her, I
said, um, my son doesn't
want to tell the police.
And she, I guess, wants
to protect him.
She wants to protect his
reputation.
That's not my plan, man.
Right?
I've been shot here two
times.
I'm an important guy.
You do something to me,
you going to jail.
Right?
If I, if I do
something, I'm going to own
up to it, man.
I ain't did nothing right.
And it ain't right.
It's not right.
How Minnesota doing, man?
Because it is on Facebook
every day, man.
These little gooses making posts.
They make, my son, they
it up, man.
Forget about the injury.
They it up, too, man.
It's, oh, it ain't right,
man.