Please be accurate with technical
terms, proper nouns, and punctuation.
I know what you guys
was going to do to
me, sir. I knew it
already, man. I knew it
already.
Where's the emergency? What's happening
there? What's happening there? Where
is the suspect?
What is your name, please?
Okay, you need to talk
to a medical dispatcher. Hold
on one, please.
Okay, get them here now.
Okay, we're sending calls. We're
sending calls right now.
What part of the body
was she shot? I don't
know. Just hurry up. Okay,
is she awake?
Listen to me. We've got
help coming right now, okay?
Okay, hurry up. Are you
next to her that
you can start CPR? No.
Or if you can help
her. Then don't do that,
okay? Careful. St. Paul Police.
See the bullet hole? It's
the cops. Open the door.
Police. Come in. Come in.
Come in. Hurry. Hurry. Don't
call. Hurry.
I don't know how many
people are up there. Don't
let them come out. She's
right on the ground.
We'll just need one medic
to come up. Yeah, I
see that. There's one. Watch
where you're
stepping. Here, one victim's right
here. One victim. She's got
a wound right under the
eye.
Do we have one more?
Just one. Just one. Okay.
Open the door. You could
just stay out, because he
has to just, you know
what I'm saying?
Okay. Where is she, bud?
She's right here. She was
unresponsive when we arrived. She
what?
Unresponsive. She's right here. She
passed away. I mean, it's
traumatic. It's a traumatic arrest.
Whatever you guys want to
do. Oh, we're done. I
mean, she is. It's a
bullet hole, right?
Right. It's a traumatic arrest.
She has a PA of
about 30. Yeah, we're just
calling it.
No, I just, maybe she
called it to love it.
I will work on getting
you a name. Just being
tight for you.
They walked through the house,
the porch, they banged on
the door. We asked who
was it.
They didn't say nothing.
What did you guys see?
White GMC. I swear to
God, white GMC.
White GMC?
Yes.
Did you see who shot?
Newer, older?
I just said he saw
a white GMC.
I don't know.
Okay.
All right.
Hold on.
Just stay.
I'm sorry.
Just stay here.
Okay.
365.
You're lying.
Suspects came in a white
GMC truck.
That's JJ's dad.
I just said that.
Oh, my God.
Did you see who the
shooter was?
Okay.
We had an incident here
a few days ago.
What's his name?
And my brother's friend, he
had died in the incident.
And that was his dad
that just came and shot
my mom.
His dad?
What's his name?
You know.
His name is Terrell Johnson.
That's his name?
Terrell Darrell Johnson.
And did you see him?
What?
Did you see him?
No, we didn't see him.
Why do you think it's
him?
Because I know his truck.
Because his truck.
I know his truck.
I know.
I swear I know.
I'm not going to.
I know.
How old is this?
How old is Terrell?
I don't know how old
he is.
Is he older?
I mean, is he 20?
Is he 40?
We don't know.
What did you guys see
in here?
We didn't see or hear
anything.
Nothing?
Were you guys here?
Yes.
Okay.
We was just up there
playing board games.
Okay.
We was just playing board
games.
Yeah.
Then somebody knocked on her
door.
She went to go see
who it was, and they
shot her.
Okay.
And then you saw the
white GMC take off?
Which way did it go?
It went this way.
The car was parked this
way.
Yeah.
Was this the touch -on?
That way towards Bain?
Yes, it went this way.
Touch -on.
I can't see past the
stop sign.
Okay.
I can't see past, like,
the ballot room.
If I can see the
pizza store, I can see
that.
Yes, the house is clear.
I haven't gone back there
yet.
Have you guys?
Terrell Johnson.
Terrell.
Terrell Darrell Johnson.
After G .J. got shot.
Yes.
Everybody's number.
Oh, my God.
I already did.
When was the last time
you guys saw each other?
I haven't seen Darnell at
all.
You got to know.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
That's G .J.
I can't see him.
Do you know where Terrell
lives?
No, I don't.
He said it was a
white game.
It's like a...
It's like Chuck.
Right.
That's the last time you
saw him.
Was there anything that you
saw about...
Like, was it a new...
I don't know how long.
Was it new, old...
It was like a new
arrangement.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know.
I can't see, but it
was...
Like a big, like a
full -size SUV?
Yeah, when they're done.
Okay.
My bad.
I didn't mean to call
you.
What do you think?
When was the last time
you saw that car parked
outside?
About, like, a few days
ago.
Right after JJ got trapped?
Have you seen it at
all today?
This was private, bro.
You have to think about
it.
He came here one day,
tried to come in.
Nobody opened the door.
Then he just came back.