Please, please, the violence in
this town is out of
control.
Somebody is going to jail.
Sit up.
Bullet hole.
Careful.
St. Paul Police!
See the bullet hole?
It's the police!
It's the cops!
Open the door!
Come on, look!
No!
It's the police!
Come in, come in!
Hurry, hurry!
It's the police!
Hurry!
Don't talk!
Get out of the way!
See the...
Come here.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no.
Tell me what was...
Hey, there's nothing here.
What did this woman want
to do?
Tell me.
She was unresponsive when we
arrived.
She what?
Unresponsive.
No, not that.
She is a...
Let me stop.
Had this dream already of
this.
I know what you guys
are going to do to
me, sir.
I know it already, man.
I know it already.
I don't know what's the
emergency.
What's happening there?
Mom, she got shot.
Where is the suspect?
I don't know.
What is your name, please?
Okay, do you need to
talk to a medical...
Do you need to talk
to a medical dispatcher?
Hold on one, please.
Come here now.
I will talk to whoever.
Okay, listen to me now.
Where is that being called
right now?
What part of the body
was she shot?
I don't know.
Just hurry.
Okay.
She awake?
Listen to me.
We've got...
Help's coming right now, okay?
Hurry up.
Are you not scared that
you can start CPR?
No, I'm hurt.
Okay, sit next to her
so you can help her.
Mom, I'm scared.
Okay, then don't do it.
Then don't do that, okay?
Pull it, Paul.
Careful.
St. Paul Police.
See the bullet hole?
It's the police.
It's the cops.
Open the door.
It's the police.
No.
St. Paul Police.
Come here.
Hurry.
It's the police.
Don't.
Yeah.
Don't do this.
See that?
Come here.
Oh, yeah.
St. Paul Police.
No.
Do it.
You start it.
We don't talk.
I don't know.
We'll talk to the doctors.
And police.
All right.
Go.
I didn't have to.
I don't know.
I don't know how many
people are up there.
To the whole partner.
Don't let them come out.
Don't.
Squad 387.
We'll just leave that medic
to come out.
Shot the little boy.
Yeah.
See that?
There's one.
One out.
Come on.
I'm going to do it.
You could just stay out
because he has to just...
All right.
You know what I'm saying?
Okay.
That's a well -known arrival.
Where are you going?
She was right here.
She was unresponsive when we
arrived.
She what?
Unresponsive.
She was like, thank you.
May I stop?
She passed away.
Sister, yeah.
I mean, it's traumatic.
It's a traumatic arrest.
Whatever you guys want to
do.
Oh, we're done.
I mean, she is...
Yes.
It's a well -involved, right?
Here.
Why are you...
It's not a...
Why is he...
All right.
Right.
It's a traumatic arrest.
He's a PA of a
boss party.
Oh, I'm glad.
I'm close.
I think...
Yeah, we're just calling it.
Hi.
All right.
I'm 64.
Oh.
Who are you looking for?
Hey, but...
Hey, he's nothing.
I'm rants.
What?
What's...
So, are you...
Is China any football for
me?
Dude, I don't know what
they got there.
What is it?
The black...
Oh, the old...
It's over the window.
I just...
Maybe she pulled it to
look at it.
Plank it.
Pulled the drawer.
All right.
I will work on getting
you a name.
Right.
Just in case.
All right.
They walked through the porch.
They banged on the door.
We asked who was it.
They didn't say nothing.
What did you guys see?
White GMC.
I saw that White GMC.
White GMC?
Yes.
White GMC.
White GMC who shot up?
Newer or older?
I was going to say
he saw White GMC.
All right.
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
Just stay here.
Okay.
3 -6 -5.
You're lying.
I heard you say a
suspect came in a White
GMC.
That's JJ Dad.
I just sat there.
Oh, my God.
Did you see who the
shooter was?
Okay.
We had an incident here
a few days ago.
What's his name?
And my brother Frank, he
had died in an incident.
And that was his dad
that just came to shot
my mom.
What was his name?
His name is Terrell Johnson.
That's his name?
Terrell Durell Johnson.
And did you see him?
What?
Did you see him?
No, we didn't see him.
Why do you think it's
him?
Because.
Because it's Trump.
I know.
I swear I know.
I've never.
I don't.
How old is this?
How old is he?
I don't know how old
he is.
Is he older?
I mean, is he 20?
Is he 40?
We don't know.
What did you guys see
in here?
This is.
We didn't see or hear
anything.
Nothing.
Were you guys here?
Yes.
We was just upstairs playing
board games.
Yeah.
And somebody knocked on her
door.
She went to go see
who it was and they
shot her.
Okay.
And then you saw the
white GMC take off.
Which way did it go?
Wait.
This way.
Car was parked this way.
That way towards Maine?
This way.
Yes.
I can't see past this
outside.
Okay.
I can't see past like.
I'm not white.
I can see the pizza
thorns.
I can see that.
Yes.
The house is clear.
I haven't gone back there
yet.
Have you guys?
Can you do these dance?
In the trail.
Terrell Johnson.
Terrell.
Terrell Darrell Johnson.
After G .J. got shot.
Yes.
Everybody's number.
Oh, my God.
I already did.
When was the last time
you guys saw each other?
I haven't seen Darnell at
all.
You got to know.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
That's G .J.
I can't see him.
Do you know where Terrell
lives?
No, I don't.
He said it was a
white game.
It's like a...
It's like Chuck.
Right.
That's the last time you
saw him.
Was there anything that you
saw about...
Like, was it a new...
I don't know how long.
Was it new, old...
It was like a new
arrangement.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know.
I can't see, but it
was...
Like a big, like a
full -size SUV?
Yeah, when they're done.
Okay.
My bad.
I didn't mean to call
you.
What do you think?
When was the last time
you saw that car parked
outside?
About, like, a few days
ago.
Right after JJ got trapped?
Have you seen it at
all today?
This was private, bro.
You have to think about
it.
He came here one day,
tried to come in.
Nobody opened the door.
Then he just came back.