My partner's going to kind
of talk to you about
what you're doing.
Do you have any idea
what I don't hear?
I do.
Tell me about that.
So, my kid gets shots
in the face.
What's his name?
Terrell Johnson, man.
Okay.
So, my kid gets shot
in the face.
The guy that shot him,
his mother, gets injured or
whatever,
and the kid said to
my kid's mother,
well, it might be your
dad that killed my mom.
I'm not killing nobody, man.
My son got shot, man.
That's it, man.
My son got shot.
That's it.
I just bypassed.
They know that.
Man, they know how I
look and everything, man.
They know how I look.
They asked that lady,
hey, how do your baby
daddy look?
They know how I look.
Tell me about when you
said you bypassed.
What does that mean?
Since my sons got shot,
I bypassed, and I go
see.
I asked it.
They told me and my
kid's mother.
They didn't want to tell
us a story about what
happened to my kid.
We don't feel like talking
right now.
And I said, okay, well,
I'll come to you, and
I'll bypass every day.
I mean, we cool.
I'm like you guys' dad
as well.
Yeah.
Why wouldn't you want to
talk to me?
Yeah.
That's it.
You guys have known each
other a long time.
Yeah.
They played on my son's
basketball team for seven years,
man.
Okay.
That's a chunk.
Yeah.
It's kind of weird that
I'm here.
I read the signs and
stuff, and I'm like,
this is some stuff, man,
pertaining to kids, man.
That ain't my lifestyle.
You understand me?
Is it not right to
me this isn't the first
time that this has happened
over here?
Right.
My son's been shot once
before in McDonough Projects from
her house.
Okay.
Right.
Their house gets shot up
in Mount Airy.
Oh, I'm telling my son
every time,
why would you hang with
somebody that has brothers?
You don't hang with three
brothers.
You don't hang with your
mother, son.
He's three friends and a
stranger.
He don't get it until
this happens to him.
He gets shot in the
face.
It hurt my heart to
death.
It hurt me and my
family.
But I'm not doing nothing
with no lady, my man.
I'm an adult.
If I'm going to do
something, it's going to be
the dude that did something
to my child.
I still feel that same
way.
I want him to die
before me.
I want that.
Yeah.
He hurt my child.
But I'm not going to
hurt nobody, man.
So I'm going to need
to be at homicide.
Okay.
All right.
You said you just drive
by them.
Have you tried to make
contact with them there?
Yes, we have.
We got text messages and
everything, man.
Tell me about that.
We text them and ask
them the story.
Who is them?
Mari.
Mari is the oldest son.
Okay.
She has like three boys.
And they're all the same
age group.
My son.
If you go on Facebook,
this is what they said.
They said.
So we didn't know a
story.
Okay.
My son is, he was
so messed up that he
couldn't talk for a while.
So he couldn't say a
story or he didn't do
anything.
And I'm not with his
mother.
And when I go down
there, they didn't let me
in because.
Down at the hospital?
Yeah.
Okay.
Her other, her boyfriend is
there, but her husband, you
know, because they've been together
for about six years.
But they didn't let me
in, whatever.
I sat down there.
Me and the guy get
into an altercation.
The husband?
Yeah.
Okay.
And I go on Facebook.
I'm angry.
I'm upset.
I say her name on
the thing and everything.
I say his name as
well.
The next day, she contacts
my mother.
And we, me and her
are talking without him.
And she's telling me how
she.
Uh, talk to him and
stuff.
And then I'm telling her
while I ride past her
all the time.
And I see the little
dudes standing out there and,
you know what I mean?
I, I, you know, I
asked them and they told
me the same thing, right?
I'm like, they going to
talk, he going to actually
just wait till JJ come
around.
When JJ came around, um,
the little guys, they keep
texting them and stuff.
Right.
And like, um, trying to
give him a story.
Because Jarrell was supposed to
be unconscious or something to
where he didn't know what
happened.
So they're trying to give
him a story.
Okay.
He says, the lady come
in and she keeps saying,
is you going to tell
him my son or something
or, um, giving him the
story?
And she said, I'm going
to tell the police that
you came here.
Don't tell him that you
got shot here or something.
He was saying, right?
And when you say the
lady, who are you talking
about?
Um.
The lady you're telling, you
said the lady's telling him
the story.
The lady, he said it's
a lady.
It's a, it's an adult
at the house.
Okay.
As well.
So she's telling him that,
um, don't tell the cops
that he got shot here.
There at that house.
Exactly.
That's it.
That's all we knew.
That's the only story he
said.
And I said, well, and
like I told her, I
said, um, my son doesn't
want to tell the police.
And she, I guess, wants
to protect his reputation.
That's not my plan, man.
Right?
I've been shot here two
times.
I'm an important guy.
You do something to me,
you going to jail.
Right?
If I, if I do
something, I'm going to own
up to it, man.
I ain't did nothing right.
And it ain't right.
It's not right.
How Minnesota doing, man?
Because it is on Facebook
every day, man.
It is on Facebook every
day, man.