I'm trying to, I'm trying
to tell, I'm telling you
exactly what we're seeing, and
I'm asking you to explain
that.
Okay, you've told us that
you drive in circles, you
go around to these different
young boys' houses, and you
tell me that you haunt
the horn and everything else.
You tell me that you
and your girlfriend are the
only ones that drive that
vehicle.
Yeah, I talk, yeah.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
I'm telling you exactly what
we're seeing. I'm asking for
an explanation. I'm trying to
understand.
Okay. I don't know when
you're actually talking about.
I'm talking about the night
Ms. Nix was killed.
Like I said, it's been
so much s*** that's been
going on, and I ride
by those kids' house numerous,
right, on a day, every
day, right?
So, I don't know. I'm
not, I can't give you
an answer to that because
I'm not sure, right?
Okay.
When I'm there, when I
ride around and stuff.
These little places, like I
said, I don't know what's
be going on, what's going
to happen, or anything.
So, I just be riding.
Blowing.
Everybody knows it's JJ Dad.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey.
Hey, this is the little
boy.
That's it.
I don't know about anything
else.
I don't know about no
shots.
murders.
No anything in that nature,
my brother.
I know.
I was getting the shots.
That down response as well,
I was like, you know,
the way that you guys
are looking at me, and
the way that you're acting
towards me, and make me
shut down.
This is the deal.
Your emotions that you had
when you came in here,
those are real.
You're hurting for your son.
I'm hurting.
Your son's s*** right now.
He's still hurting.
My son just got out
of the hospital yesterday.
And he's still got a
long road of recovery.
It's going to take some
time.
But what we're telling you,
I believe that too.
And there's some stuff in
your story that has been
accurate.
That has been truthful.
About you driving by.
We have several videos of
you driving by.
Which has verified that, just
like you said.
And we believe that.
You were there, in front
of that house, at the
time that shooting happened.
Doing the doot doot doot
with your horn too.
So that's why my partner's
asking you to explain it.
You get one opportunity to
tell your side of the
story of what happened.
But you were there in
front of that house at
that time of the shooting.
Not just me.
It was other people there
too.
Alright, but you also have
to understand.
Put yourself, let's switch roles
here, right?
Put yourself on this side
of the table.
I did, I did.
I know, that's why I
asked.
I know, I know, I
know.
I know it looks bad,
but...
You were pissed off.
I can't corroborate what you
guys are saying.
You were pissed off.
You were angry that this
was happening.
I didn't f***ing do nothing.
Come on, man.
Man, I didn't do nothing,
man.
I'm telling you that.
You didn't hear a shot.
I'm seriously telling you.
I didn't do anything.
I want to do something
to the little boy.
That harmed my son.
Did you mean to do
it to him and you
hit her accidentally?
No, ma 'am.
Mr. Johnson, the look of
surprise on your face.
You gotta be kidding me.
You're a smart guy.
You hear the words that
are coming out of your
mouth?
You're putting yourself on the
block, right?
Honking the horn at the
time of this thing.
And you're telling us you
didn't hear a shot.
Are you on something?
Are you a drinker?
Do you use any drugs?
I mean, is there an
explanation for this?
Help us understand this.
That's all this is.
I mean, help us understand
it.
The understanding is I didn't
touch anybody, mommy.
I didn't touch anybody.
I didn't see.
Yeah, we didn't see you
touch somebody.
I did not touch anybody.
I did not do anything.
I didn't shoot any guns.
You'll catch a knife in
my car.
I don't have any guns.
At all.
I'm trying to be as
honest as straight up.
As front.
You aren't to a portion
and then you stop.
Would you guys?
Is that true?
Because I.
This is your chance to
get it off of you.
You have to understand these
kids recognize you.
They know who you are
just like you know who
they are.
Yes, I know.
They've been with me.
So they've seen you as
you left out of there.
They've been with me for
eight years plus.
Okay.
So these kids like the
little other J .J. kid,
he would know who you
are.
Or the other.
Yes.
The kids that live there.
All of them.
You don't think that they
didn't see you leave from
there after their mom was
shot?
Miss Lady.
Killed on the ground right
in front of them?
And her grandbaby?
I didn't kill nobody, man.
I didn't kill nobody.
I tell you that.
Tell us what happened, Mr.
Johnson.
That's what happened, sir.
You haven't really told us
anything.
What do you mean that's
what happened?
That's what I did.
What did you do?
I just drove around.
Just drove around?
I just drove around, man.
In your mind's eye.
Give me your mind's eye
for me.
Get on cook like you're
driving up to the street.
You're driving up to the
house.
Right?
Tell me what you're seeing.
Tell me what you're hearing.
Tell me what happens.
Nothing.
No.
Nothing at all.
Okay.
I can't believe that.
Just based...
It was just you and
I talking.
Right?
And I didn't have these
other things.
You wasn't afforded this video
with audio.
You wasn't going to believe
me anyways.
Are you sure?
Positive.
You gave me...
If I understood.
Right?
If I understood from you.
But you're not telling me
anything.
You're just telling me you
drove by.
You were there honking the
horn, whatever.
But you didn't...
You didn't hear a gunshot.
You would never understand.
Try me.
I did what you would
do.
Okay.
And you guys put me
over here and interrogate me
and try to give me
a story that you make
up for me.
When I told you what
happened, I told you about
my son being like that.
Right?
You did.
You guys ain't...
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
And I am.
And I truly mean that.
I'm a father myself.
It's not active.
How do you know?
Because I know.
Because I see the little
dude on Facebook showing my
son gun.
He said...
And he said...
That's what I mean.
It's not active.
Have you talked to an
investigator?
Little dude's face.
Have you talked to an
investigator?
No, ma 'am.
So before you say that
it's inactive, you need to
get the facts on it.
And that's the thing.
I'm not putting it in
making a story yet.
I'm basing it on the
facts that I've been spending
for the last week and
me and my partner have.
On facts that we've gathered
in evidence to put you
in this spot.
We didn't put you in
here.
We didn't just go pick
you up just randomly.
It's based on evidence that
we've gathered and it's facts.
Okay.
Straight facts.
Okay?
It's not...
I'm just in.
I'm trying to understand what
happened.
Because what I'm looking at,
I think I know what
happened.
Okay?
I'm pretty sure I do.
And you keep telling me
that I...
If you knew what happened,
you would go and get
the...
Look at that dude instead
of having me down here.
Really?
That's what you would do.
Yeah.
Who did it then?
Because the fact is, my
son is shot in the
face.
Nobody's down.
I'm down here.
I wasn't actually...
Whoa.
Did you have an alibi
or...
No, anything.
I'm just automatically guilty because
you seen my car.
I didn't even...
I didn't even do anything.
And then...
I'm seriously telling you.
I did not do anything.
I want to do something
to the little boy that
harmed my son.
Did you mean to do
it to him and you
hit her accidentally?
No, ma 'am.
Mr. Johnson, the look of
surprise on your face.
You got to be kidding
me.
You're a smart guy.
You have the words that
are coming out of your
mouth.
You're putting yourself on the
block, right?
Honking the horn at the
time of this thing.
And you're telling us you
didn't hear a shot.
You have to understand these
kids recognize you.
They know who you are
just like you know who
they are.
Yes, I know.
They've been with me for...
So they've seen you as
you left out of there.
They've been with me for
eight years plus.
Okay.
So these kids like the
little other J .J. kid,
he would know who you
are or the other kids
that live there.
All of them.
You don't think that they
didn't see you leave from
there after their mom was
shot?
Miss Lady.
Killed on the ground right
in front of them?
And her grandbaby?
I didn't kill nobody, man.
I didn't kill nobody, I
tell you that.
That's...
I did what you would
do, okay?
Okay.
You guys put me over
here and interrogate me and
try to give me a
story that you make up
for me.
When I told you what
happened, I told you about
my son being like that,
right?
You did.
You guys ain't...
Start over.
I'm basing it on the
facts that I've been spending
for the last week and
me and my partner have.
On facts that we've gathered
in evidence to put you
in this spot.
We didn't put you in
here.
We didn't just go pick
you up just randomly.
It's based on evidence that
we've gathered and it's facts.
Okay.
Straight facts, okay?
It's not...
I understand.
Mr. Johnson, you got upset
with us when we told
you about the evidence that
we do have
and I just asked you
to simply just to explain,
to try to explain and
help us understand how we
got it wrong.
You know what I mean?
Can you help us?
Because we're not there.
I was going to say,
yay, you didn't get it
wrong, man.
You got to do what
you have to do because
that's your job.
I'm going to ask you,
these clothes and stuff, you
still have those clothes?
That ain't me.
That's not you?
No.