I'm trying to tell, I'm
telling you exactly what we're
seeing, and I'm asking you
to explain that.
Okay, you've told us that
you drive in circles, you
go around to these different
young boys' houses,
and you tell me that
you haunt the horn and
everything else.
You tell me that you
and your girlfriend are the
only ones that drive that
vehicle.
Yeah, I talk, yeah.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
I'm telling you exactly what
we're seeing. I'm asking for
an explanation, trying to understand.
Okay, I don't know when
you're actually talking about.
I'm talking about the night
Ms. Nix was killed.
Like I said, it's been
so much s*** that's been
going on, and I ride
by those kids' house numerous,
right, on a day, every
day, right?
So I don't know, I'm
not, I can't give you
an answer to that because
I'm not sure, right?
Okay.
When I'm there, when I
ride around and stuff.
These little places, like I
said, I don't know what's
be going on, what's going
to happen, or anything.
So I just be riding,
blowing.
Everybody know this is JJ
Dad.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey.
Hey, this is the little
boy.
That's it.
I don't know about anything
else.
I don't know about no
shots.
murders, no anything in that
nature, my brother.
I know I was getting
the s***.
Now, response as well, I
was like, you know, the
way that you guys are
looking at me and the
way that you're acting towards
me, it make me shut
down.
This is the deal.
Your emotions that you had
when you came in here,
those are real.
You're hurting for your son.
I'm hurting.
Your son's s*** right now.
He's still hurting.
My son just got out
of the hospital yesterday.
And he's still got a
long road of recovery.
It's going to take some
time.
But what we're telling you,
I believe that too.
And there's some stuff in
your story that has been
accurate and has been.
Truthful about you driving by.
We have several videos of
you driving by, which has
verified that, just like you
said.
And we believe that you
were there in front of
that house at the time
that shooting happened, doing the
doot, doot, doot with your
horn, too.
So that's why my partner
is asking you to explain
it.
You get one opportunity to
tell your side of the
story of what happened.
But you were there in
front of that house at
that time of the shooting.
Not just me.
It was other people there,
too.
You're not being a c***,
alright, but you also have
to understand, I mean, put
yourself, let's switch roles.
Here, right?
Put yourself on this side
of the table.
I did.
I know.
That's why I know.
What you're telling.
I know it looks bad,
but you were pissed off.
I can't cooperate.
You guys are sorry.
As if I don't agree
that this is how I
can do nothing.
Come on, man.
Man, I didn't do nothing,
man.
I'm telling you that you
didn't hear a shot.
I'm seriously telling you, I
did not do anything.
I want to do something
to the little boy.
That harmed my son.
Did you mean to do
it to him and you
hit her accidentally?
No, ma 'am.
Mr.
Johnson, the look of surprise
on your face.
You got to be kidding
me.
You're a smart guy.
You hear the words that
are coming out of your
mouth.
You're putting yourself on the
block, right?
Honking the horn at the
time of this thing.
And you're telling us you
didn't hear a shot.
Are you on something?
Are you a drinker?
Do you use any drugs?
I mean, is there an
explanation for this?
No.
Help us understand this.
That's all this is.
I mean, help us understand
it.
The understanding is I didn't
touch anybody, mommy.
I didn't touch anybody.
I didn't say.
Yeah, we didn't say you
took something.
I did not touch anybody.
I did not do anything.
I didn't shoot any guns.
You'll catch a knife in
my car.
I don't have any guns
at all.
I'm trying to be as
honest as straight up as
you are to abortion.
And then you stop when
you guys are true.
Because this is your chance
to get it off of
you.
You have to understand these
kids recognize you.
They know who you are,
just like you know who
they are.
Yes, I know.
They've been with me.
So they've seen you as
you left out of there.
They've been with me for
eight years plus.
OK, so these kids, like
the little other J .J.
kid, he would know who
you are or the other
kids that live there.
All of them.
You don't think that they
didn't see you leave from
there after their mom was
shot?
Miss Lady. Killed on the
ground right in front of
them.
And her grandbaby.
I didn't kill nobody, man.
I didn't kill nobody.
I tell you that that's
what happens.
That's what happened, sir.
You haven't really told us
anything.
We mean, that's what happened.
That's that's that's what that's
what I did.
What did you do?
I just drove around.
Just drove around. I just
drove around.
And just in your mind's
eye, in your mind's eye
for me.
You know, cook like you're
driving up to the street,
driving up to the house.
Right. Tell me what you're
saying.
Tell me what you're hearing.
Tell me what happens.
Nothing, nothing at all.
I can't believe that just
based it was just you
and I talking.
Right. And I didn't have
these other things.
You wasn't afforded this this
video with audio.
You wasn't going to believe
me anyway.
Are you sure? Positive.
If you gave me that,
if I understood.
Right. If I understood from
you.
But you're not telling me
anything.
You're telling me you drove
by.
You were there honking the
horn, whatever.
But you didn't hear you
didn't hear a gunshot.
You would never understand.
Try me. I did what
you would do.
OK. And you guys put
me over here
and interrogate me and try
to give me a story
that you make up for
me.
When I told you what
happened, I told you about
my son being like that.
Right. You did.
You guys.
I'm sorry. And I truly
mean that.
I'm a father myself.
It's not active. How do
you know?
Because I know I see
because I see the little
dude on Facebook showing my
son gun.
He said and he said,
oh, I mean, it's not
active.
Little little dude's face.
Have you talked to an
investigator? No.
So before you say that
it's inactive, you need to
get the facts on it.
And that's the thing. I'm
not making a story yet.
I'm based on the facts
that I've been
spending for the last week
and me and my partner
have on facts that we've
gathered
in evidence to put you
in.
This spot. We didn't put
you in here.
We didn't just go pick
you up just randomly.
It's based on evidence that
we've gathered.
And it's facts.
OK, straight facts.
OK, it's not.
I'm just trying to understand
what happened.
Is it because because what
I'm looking at, I think
I know what happened.
I'm pretty sure I do.
You keep telling me that
if you knew what happened,
you would get the idea.
And instead of having me
out here, that's what you
would do.
Well, yeah. Who did it
then?
Because of the fact.
My son is shot in
the face.
Nobody's down.
I'm down here.
I wasn't asked, well, did
you have an alibi or
know anything?
I'm just automatically guilty because
you've seen my car.
I didn't even I didn't
even do anything.
I didn't even do any
game.
And then I'm seriously telling
you, you know, I do
anything.
I want to do something
to the little boy that
harmed my son.
Did you mean to him?
Did you hit him and
you hit her accidentally?
No, ma 'am. No, ma
'am.
No, ma 'am.
Mr. Johnson, the look of
surprise on your face.
You got to be kidding
me. You're a smart guy.
You have the words that
are coming out of your
mouth.
You're putting yourself on the
block, right?
Honking the horn at the
time of this thing.
And you're telling us you
didn't hear a shot.
You have to understand these
kids recognize you.
They know who you are,
just like you know who
they are.
Yes, I know.
They've been they've seen you
and you left out of
there.
They've been with me for
eight years.
Plus, OK, so these kids,
like the little other J
.J.
kid, he would know you
or the other.
Yes, the kids that live
there.
All of you don't think
that they didn't see you
leave from there after their
mom
was shot, mislead, killed on
the ground right in front
of them and her grandbaby.
I didn't kill nobody, man.
I didn't kill nobody.
I tell you that that
I did what you would
do.
OK, and you guys put
me over here and interrogate
me and try to give
me a story that you
make up for me when
I told you what happened.
I told you about my
son being like that.
Right. You did.
You guys think I'm based
on the facts that I've
been spending for the last
week
and me and my partner
have on facts that we've
gathered in evidence to put
you in this spot.
We didn't put you in
here.
We didn't just go pick
you up just randomly.
It's based on evidence that
we've gathered and it's facts.
OK.
It's not.
I understand.
Mr. Johnson, you got upset
with us when we told
you about the evidence that
we do
have, and I just asked
you to simply just to
explain and try to explain
and help us
understand how how we got
it wrong.
You know what I mean?
Can you help us?
Because we're not we're not
there.
I was going to say,
yeah, you didn't you didn't
get it wrong, man.
You've got to do what
you have to do, because
that's your job.
I'm going to ask you
these clothes and stuff.
These clothes.
Do you still have those
clothes?
That ain't me.
That's not you?
No.