Please, please. The violence in
this town is out of
control. Somebody is going to
jail.
Sit up. Pull it, Bull.
Careful. St. Paul Police! See
the bullet hole?
It's the police! It's the
cops! Open the door!
It's the police! Come in,
come in!
Hurry, hurry!
Alex!
Jesus!
Come here. Come here.
Oh, no!
Tell her what was...
Hey, it's nothing, man.
What did this woman want
to do?
So, hey, she was unresponsive
when we arrived.
She what?
Unresponsive.
She was like, stay here.
Let me stop.
I had this dream already
of this. I know what
you guys are going to
do to me, sir.
I knew it already, man.
I knew it already.
I don't know what's the
emergency.
Audrey!
What's happening there?
Monty got shot!
Where is the suspect?
I don't know.
What is your name, please?
Okay, do you need to
talk to a medical...
Do you need to talk
to a medical dispatcher? Hold
on one, please.
I'm here now. I will
talk to whoever.
Okay, listen to me now.
Where is that being pulled
right now?
What part of the body
was she shot?
I don't know.
Just hurry.
Okay.
She awake?
Listen to me.
We've got help coming right
now, okay?
Hurry up!
Are you not scared that
you can start CPR?
No, I'm hurt!
Okay, sit next to her
so you can help her.
Mom, I'm scared!
Okay, then don't do it.
Then don't do that, okay?
Bullet hole.
Careful.
St. Paul Police!
See the bullet hole?
It's the police!
It's the cops! Open the
door!
It's the police!
No!
St. Paul Police!
Come in, come in!
Hurry! Hurry!
I'm going to call the
police!