So they got that. I
understand that. But now we
got to talk about why
we're here.
Exactly.
So what's going through your
mind then when you're driving
by these boys' houses? Tell
me about that.
The only thing that's going
through my mind is, they're
like my son. I want
to know what happened to
my son, man.
Sure.
What happened to my son,
my brother?
Of those addresses, did you
ever get out and make
contact with anybody at any
of those addresses?
Addresses?
I get out. Yeah, I
get out. I knock on
the door.
Okay. Tell me how that
goes.
Sometimes I talk to the
little guys, and sometimes no
one answers.
Lately, it's been pitch black.
When I go down the
street, all the lights is
out.
So I'm saying in my
head, okay, I know. I
already know that you guys
had to do it to
him.
But you know what? I'm
not his mother.
I said, when I see
my son, I was going
to...
I'm going to press him
and make him do it.
Somebody is going to jail
for what they did to
him, man.
When you go by these
houses, were you alone, or
would you go with anybody?
It varies, because after it
happened to him, I go
by there every single day.
I stay right here on
the east side as well.
So I would frequently just
go by when I'm crying
or whatever.
I want those guys to
see my tears so they
can understand as well.
Man, this is a serious
matter, man.
What happened to the little
dude?
Man, you might be in
danger, right?
But I knew that they
wasn't in danger.
I knew that they did
that to him.
You're hurting.
Yes.
What do you drive? Is
it the car that you
got stopped in?
I got a blue Chrysler
300.
And what else do you
drive?
The white truck that I
was just in.
I drive that as well.
Either if I'm not in
the Chrysler, then I'm in...
The truck, because my girlfriend,
we...
It was a 9mm, and
he had, like, an extended
magazine on there.
Do you know what brand?
I don't know what brand.
Now, the reason I know
that is because me and
my mother is in the
car,
and just like I just
picking her up from work
and stuff,
and we left work, and
we're just driving down Payne,
and I see my son.
And I tell him, get
in the car.
Hey, boy, you eat today?
Because I'm not in his
household.
But it's like my little
brother as well as my
son.
So he gets in the
car, and I can tell.
I see it on him.
And I just grabbed it.
And me and my mother
was talking, and she was
kind of mad at me.
But I said, hey, man,
look, I don't know what
type of lifestyle you into,
right?
I'm not going to take
it from you because I
don't know if you need
it.
If I would have...
If I would have took
it, my son wouldn't have
been shot.
So that's hurting you.
That definitely hurts me.
Did you ever carry a
gun?
I've had it, yeah.
Okay.
Have you carried a gun
since this happened to your
son?
No.
You'll see what I got.
It's a knife in the
truck.
No guns for me, man.
That's what I say, man.
Look, man, just from implicating
me, it get bad for
me, right?
That's what I was trying
to tell.
The little guys, I haven't
seen those guys since they
told my kid's mother that
stuff, right?
About you being involved and
that lady getting hurt.
Exactly.
Now, before that, they will
see me.
So after they told her,
they never see me again.
Made me think you guys
really think about me.
You said geranium, the address
where the lady got hurt.
You said geranium.
Was that Cook?
The street?
Yeah.
I drive everywhere.
The kid's house is on
Cook, yes.
Where your son got shot?
Yes, that's where my son
got shot.
Okay.
Is that one of the
addresses that you drive by?
Yes.
It is.
Okay.
When she got hurt, right,
and I'm just going to
keep it real with you,
she wasn't just
hurt.
She was killed.
I know.
I heard that.
You know that.
That's why, yeah.
How long did it take
before you found out about
that?
The next day.
So when was the last
time?
Before that lady got killed,
that you were on that
block, that you drove by
that house?
I'm not sure.
I drove by a lot,
all the time.
Were you on that street?
Were you on Cook the
night that she was killed?
I was not, but I
did go through there that
day.
That day?
Yeah.
Do you have any idea
what time it was?
I got receipts from Dollar
General.
Me and my girlfriend went
to the store.
Remember if the sun was
up or the sun was
down?
Okay.
In that general bathroom?
Dollar is the name of
it.
I'm familiar with it.
That's the store that's right
next to the house where
she was killed?
Yeah.
Okay.
So you and your girlfriend
were there and purchased some
things?
Yeah.
I ride around in a
circle and a loop.
Okay.
The whole little basketball team
that my son used to
be with, I just ride
just to see what
they're going to do to
me.
See, because if they did
something to my son, then
they're going to shoot me
too, right?
Okay.
That's all I've been doing.
And you're driving?
No, I'm talking about -
Are you using?
I'm talking about being alert.
Okay.
If I got to go,
I'm going to go right
then, but I think my
knife will do damage.
It's a nice knife, but
hey, it is what it
is, man.
The city's got cameras.
Go up any block and
you're going to see cameras
on doorbells.
You're going to see them
on eaves of houses and
everything else.
We can see you that
night driving around, just like
you're saying, big loop.
You didn't see me driving
around.
Who else is driving that
car?
Me or my girlfriend.
Mm -hmm.
All right.
I'm going to keep it
real with you.
There's cameras right on cook.
Okay?
Okay.
Two of the cameras that
are on cook, you'll have
an opportunity to see this
and read about
it, but two of the
cameras on cook, they've got
audio as well.
All right?
And as your truck drives
by, a couple of seconds
later, we start hearing the
horn honking,
and then we hear a
door, and then we hear
a shot.
Okay?
Okay.
And then we see your
truck pull out.
Okay.
On to Payne Avenue from
a nice little camera at
the pizzeria.
Okay.
Help me understand that.
No, I don't get it.
I don't get what you're
trying to tell me to
understand to you.