Going into its third day,
a baffling mystery is unfolding
in Alton, Illinois, a river
town outside St. Louis.
Nurses' aide and mom of
four, Bonnie Woodward, vanishes in
broad daylight just before her
48th birthday.
Alton, it's a nice little
town. It's situated on the
Mississippi River and the Illinois
River.
It has a vibrant downtown,
a lot of history, and
it's a great place to
live and work.
So, with no sign of
Bonnie anywhere, her family goes
to the media, her older
brother tearfully pleading with the
public.
I want my sister. Somebody
please call us and let
us know what's going on.
We don't know nothing.
Nobody wanted this case solved
more than her siblings.
Whoever has my sister, please
let her go.
Bonnie's sister, Rebecca, and her
niece, Rachel, don't hesitate to
join in on the efforts,
making the 700 -mile ride
a success.
They'll drive to Alton from
their home in Louisiana.
Why were you concerned enough
to get in the car
and start driving?
Well, because she wouldn't just
not come home.
I just remember having a
stack of flyers and going
around and putting them on
every telephone pole that I
could.
The police naturally talked to
the people that had last
seen Bonnie.
Can I get your last
name?
Bosley B .A .U .S.
I know why.
Wanda Bosley was one of
the co -workers that worked
with Bonnie at the Eunice
Smith Nursing Home.
We have to find out
how Bonnie was during the
day.
Was she acting appropriate? Was
she, you know, upset about
anything?
Okay, and so you went
into this meeting. She was
in the meeting.
You got out around 3
o 'clock, and you, what
happened then?
So, well, at first, like,
in the meeting, I just
want to say,
Bonnie's, when she talked, she's
loud, and she seemed different
to me.
She was quiet, and her
voice was more mellow like
mine now.
And I remember thinking, man,
Bonnie seems a little different.
After that staff meeting, Wanda
says she headed to the
back parking lot to get
into her car.
Out of the corner of
her eye, she spots Bonnie.
And she's not alone.
She was standing, like, say
if this is the back
of her truck.
The guy was standing here,
and I was looking, and
Bonnie had walked up the
side of her truck to
the driver's door.
And the guy was just
standing there.
I didn't see anything strange,
but it...
Kind of seemed strange, because
I guess I had never
seen the man before.
Can you describe the guy
for me?
He was a white male.
He looked like he wasn't
very tall, maybe 5 '8",
5 '9", or so.
He was, like, a medium
-sized guy.
His hair was a salt
and pepper, more grayer than
black.
Turns out, Wanda is not
the only co -worker to
have witnessed this strange sighting.
Several people report to police
seeing this mystery man, sitting
in a gray or silver
sedan, similar to a Chevy
Malibu, waiting for Bonnie to
get out of her staff
meeting.
So, the gray Chevy Malibu
was directly to the right
of her vehicle.
Plenty of people saw him.
Yeah, after the meeting, people
would see her interacting with
him outside both vehicles, and
ultimately got into the car
with him.
She did get into the
car willingly, and it did
not appear that she was
forced or anything like that.
Vincent Altony, the public's help,
finding a missing woman, 48
-year -old Bonnie Woodward.
The information regarding the person
that people had seen on
that parking lot was crucial.
She reportedly was seen talking
to someone inside a gray
or silver Chevy Malibu.
So, talking to the family
and friends, did anybody, like
a past relationship, match the
description?
And you don't know anybody
off the top of your
head that would have a
silver Malibu?
Her ex -boyfriend, Chester, Nick
Adams.
Chester's dad has a 2009
Impala.
If you put an Impala
and a Malibu side by
side, there's just a little
bit of difference.
It'd be hard to tell
the difference.
That's true.
Who does this guy sound
like to you?
Chester McAdams.
That's the only guy I
can figure out that fits
the description that it's Chester.
I mean, I don't like
to pinpoint a guy out,
but Chester fits every description.
And like the silver Impala,
his dad has a silver
Impala.
Do you know that for
sure?
Yeah, because he used to
date my mom.
Chester McAdams.
Chester McAdams piques the detective's
interest not only because he
dated Bonnie for a year,
but he also has an
extensive criminal record.
Bonnie started to see him,
and then I showed back
up in the picture and
ran him off.
Me and Bonnie's been together
probably seven or more years.
We parted about a little
over two years, and that's
when she got with that
Chester guy.
You and Chester ever have
words?
Oh, big time.
Big time hate each other?
Oh, yeah.
Fist fights?
I ran into him at
the bar. He was mad
because me and Bonnie got
back together.
So I kind of thought
maybe he was upset and
might have did something to
her.
And, sir, for the record,
I just need your last
name.
I'm McAdams.
Capital M, small c, capital
A, D -A -M -S.
And your first, sir?
Chester.
With Chester, it was a
very rocky relationship that Bonnie
had with him.
We'd break up, she'd kick
me out, and I'd be
gone for a week or
so, and then I'd be
moving back in.
Yeah, I've been down that
road.
Okay, so then, you know,
that would be two or
three months, and then I'd
be kicked out again, and
then back and forth.
And then about two months
before Gary got out, she
kicked me out, and then
next thing I know, Gary's
living there.
The family largely was saying,
hey, you guys need to
look at Chester McAdams.
When we found Chester McAdams,
he's got a beard, he's
got a ponytail.
Chester clearly doesn't match the
description of the man coworkers
saw days earlier in the
parking lot with Bonnie.
But what about that tip
from Bonnie's daughter, Jennifer, who
said Chester's father drives a
silver Chevy Impala?
Detectives want to talk it
over with father and son.
Do you ever drive his
truck or Impala, anything like
that?
No.
Do you ever allow him
to borrow it for any
reason?
No.
I would never ask my
dad to borrow his vehicle.
He'd say no.
Well, I know I'd say
no right off the bat,
John.
Right.
Don't even bother asking.
Well, I mean, we're investigating
this missing bird.
Right.
It could be more than
missing.
I mean, look at it.
It could have a big
problem.
Yes.
And it could be nothing.
It could be nothing.
Right.
I mean, I hope it's
nothing.
Chester McAdams was willing and
cooperative with us.
Ultimately, did not have direct
access to a vehicle that
was like that.
And also, we checked in
with his employer and they
confirmed that he was at
work.
So, that was a dead
end for us.
The family of a missing
Alton woman is now offering
a $5 ,000 reward to
anyone who can find her.
You have crime in this
area, but you don't have
missing adults too often.
We have people that run
away, but they're always found.
But this one, she just
fell off the face of
the earth.
We need to find my
sister.
We're running out of time.
Everybody knows the first three
days is critical.
With both Gary and Bonnie's
ex cleared, detectives are hitting
walls left and right.
But they're about to be
floored by some information that
reveals a disturbing coincidence in
the Woodward family.
Turns out, Bonnie wasn't the
only missing person in that
household.
Correct.
I need my daddy.