Bonnie Woodward's disappearance is the
talk of the small town
in Illinois she called home.
Bonnie Woodward has been missing.
Friends and family were gathering
to pray for her return.
We need you to find
my sister. We're running out
of time.
Investigators are frustrated and increasingly
concerned.
We were doing missing person
flyers, talking to local media.
We were trying to push
this out there as much
as we can.
Maybe somebody saw her somewhere
at a bus station, at
a train station, in a
cab, at the mall.
We're trying to get any
kind of lead that'll take
us where we need to
go.
But they're all kind of
wild goose chases.
It's as if she's vanished
into thin air.
Right. It wasn't without leads.
Somebody would say they saw
somebody similar in Pontoon Beach,
Applebee's in Kansas City.
But none of them appeared
to have much merit.
We had to expand our
investigation and look into everything
about her life that was
going on at that time.
You discover, wait, she's not
the only missing person in
that household.
Right. Right.
It turns out that her...
stepdaughter, Heather Woodward, had been
reported missing to the East
Alton Police Department more than
a week before.
East Alton Police Department, which
is a separate police department
from ours.
So we were not aware
of that at the time
that Bonnie went missing.
It was nothing 100 %
that told us that the
two were linked.
So at that point, we're
having to do a dual
investigation.
This is a huge coincidence
in a small town that
a mother and stepdaughter go
missing in the same house.
Huge. Huge.
Remember, Heather Woodward is Bonnie's
17 -year -old stepdaughter.
Bonnie adopted Heather and her
brother Aaron after their dad
passed away when Heather was
just eight.
After Bonnie adopted them, it
was made very abundantly clear
they're in the family.
Those are her kids.
The house is a busy
one with Bonnie's adult daughter,
Jennifer, and her two little
girls.
Plus Heather, Aaron, and boyfriend,
Gary, all living under one
roof.
And the family tells...
For the detectives, there was
friction between Heather and Bonnie.
It was an unhappy teenager,
and it was a stepmom
giving her chores to do,
and there was a little
resistance.
At some point, they argue,
and Heather wants to move
out, and Bonnie initially doesn't
resist the idea.
Our investigation revealed that around
June 10th, Heather went with
her teacher, and that was
Christine Sheffel, and Bonnie knew
about this.
That teacher pictured in the
high school yearbook along with
Heather.
Heather moved in with her
just two weeks before Bonnie
vanished.
And now that both Bonnie
and Heather are missing, investigators
have lots of questions.
I'm here with Christine Sheffel.
I wanted to get the
history of how she became
engaged with Heather's life.
And then the number one
question is, where is she
now?
She was last with you.
Where is she at?
I have Heather now for
one class as a freshman
for the entire year.
She has been very vocal.
Both Sue, myself, and all
the other teachers of the
abuse that goes on at
home.
Things like being slapped or
thrown against a wall, or
woke up at 3 in
the morning to wash every
dish in the house.
Just plain crazy stuff.
And who's the one she's
watching that does all this?
Bonnie.
We knew that East Alton
Police Department was aware of
these reports, and we could
not get anything to substantiate
these reports.
Heather painted a picture of
your aunt.
And she was seen as
being abusive.
What do you make of
those allegations of abuse?
I can't see it.
I can see her being
loud with anybody, child or
not, and just being vocal,
but not abusive.
There was no way.
Heather has been telling everyone
for over a year that
when she turns 18, she
will be kicked out.
She called and said that
I'm getting kicked out and
I need you to come
get me.
The teachers, I believe her
heart was in the right
place as she's trying to
help this 17 -year -old.
Yeah.
Child.
Bonnie called us and wanted
Heather back.
So, and I did tell
her she had to go
back home.
So, she cried most of
the night.
And then whenever you came
back on the 17th, she
was gone.
Right.
So now, according to this
teacher, Heather leaves her home
on the 17th.
That same day, Bonnie reports
Heather as a runaway.
Bonnie went knocking on doors.
It was driving Bonnie nuts
because she couldn't find her.
In obtaining the reports.
It was clear that Bonnie
wanted to find her stepdaughter.
And she was not getting
the information she wanted from
the teacher.
And she was adamant that
no matter what, she was
going to find her.
And now, detectives aren't making
much headway in finding Heather
either.
The teacher who Heather had
been living with says she
has no idea where Heather
might have gone.
There was nothing that we
could really prove that she
knew where Heather was.
But clearly, I'm still skeptical.
Are they telling the whole
truth?
With her lack of intent
on trying to find Heather,
and if she was that
much of a mentor to
her,
why wasn't she more concerned
about Heather's whereabouts if she
didn't know?
Heather's teacher's interview only raises
more questions for investigators.
Are these disappearances linked?
And if so, how?
As investigators, you're fairly convinced
that she might have had
something to do with the
disappearance,
or at the very least,
know something.
We think the two events
have to be linked in
some way.
Two missing persons from the
same house, one a juvenile,
and the other a child.
One a juvenile and one
adult, like, you almost have
to believe they're related.
Like, it's really naive to
think they're not.
After almost a week and
no sign of Bonnie, her
family's anguish turns pointed,
lashing out at that mystery
man from the parking lot.
You let my sister go,
and I'll come and get
her. I want my sister.
I felt like Heather had
the answers that we needed.
We believed she was the
key to finding Bonnie.
And that's when police get
a game -changing phone call
from a nearby library.
I had heard it over
the sleep scanners. It was
very strange.
It seems someone showed up
there with a teddy bear
and a story to tell.
I had to pee, Mr.
Bear.