Summer is in full swing
here in Alton, Illinois. Backyard
barbecues, 4th of July fireworks.
Bonnie Woodward used to host
these kinds of events, but
not this year. She's been
missing for a week. And
in a twist, her teenage
stepdaughter is missing too. Until
out of the blue, eight
days after Bonnie vanished, through
these doors walks the missing
teenager, Heather Woodward.
The East Alton Police Department
received a call from the
library that there's a person
saying that she's Heather Woodward.
With all the speculation going
around, I wanted to hear
what she had to say.
They got Heather, took her
to the police station, and
I thought, man, they're going
to find out something now.
And would you state your
name, please?
Heather Woodward.
And your birthday, Heather?
Today.
Physical condition for Heather was
not of anything that was
of a concern.
There was no...
Injury to her. Clearly, she
had been being taken care
of.
Okay. What do you know
about the whole situation with
Bonnie and everything?
What I read in the
paper.
Okay.
That's it.
And I guess you read
in the paper that you
were also...
Yeah.
A little citizen running away
also?
And I was planning on
coming home on my birthday.
That was the plan, so
I didn't have to go
back to Bonnie's house.
I was taken back that
how can she be actually
18 years of age?
My mom claustrophobic moose, and
even my daddy.
But she's clutching a teddy
bear.
Yes.
July 3rd is her 18th
birthday, so she's a bona
fide adult in the state
of Illinois, but she talks
more like a...
Well, I don't want to
be insulting, but like a
grade school student or a
junior high student.
I need my books. I
need my books.
I need my books, books,
books, books, books.
She showed up at a
library. What did you think?
That it was absolute .
What do you mean by
that?
Like, why are you showing
up at a library? Who
brought you? Where did you
come from? Where have you
been?
Something doesn't smell right.
Pretty much.
What made the decision that
you would go to the
library? Why not to the
police department or something?
Because I always go to
the library. I walk there
all the time, and I
wasn't comfortable walking to the
police station.
Do you think you're in
any trouble?
I don't know.
I'm scared.
Yes, you had a lot
of people concerned about you.
We don't know what happened
to you. We don't know
what happened to Bonnie.
I haven't talked to my
mom.
Heather's thought of it was
it wasn't that big of
a deal that Bonnie had
disappeared.
It didn't come across to
me that she had a
lot of concern about where
Bonnie was at the time.
What do you think happened
to her?
I don't know. I thought
that maybe she hid to
draw me out, and then
she'll come out now that
she knows that I'm home.
That's what she thought? Why
would she think that?
Because sometimes that's just the
way Bonnie is, and she
can be mean, and I
don't know. She's just mean.
You know, I gave her
the safe space to talk
to me about situations in
the home, and pretty much
the extent of it was
that she was being made
to do chores and clean
the house.
You know, typical things that
I think a lot of
teenagers and youths do.
And should be doing.
Because I'm not going back
there to be slave labor
and a free babysitter. I
just couldn't do it no
more.
From what she told multiple
people, she was being physically
and verbally and mentally abused.
You know, it doesn't go
beyond the realm of possibility
that maybe she was embellishing
more about that relationship between
her and Bonnie.
To pull the heartstrings of
people that, you know, were
close to her. That could
be of assistance to her.
And one of those people...
Police begin to realize, may
have been that teacher, Christine
Scheffel, who took Heather in.
Ms. Scheffel has been there
for me for four years,
and she was afraid for
me to go home because
Bonnie can be mean, and
sometimes she hits.
There was an investigation into
Bonnie's parenting.
Yeah, it's DCFS, Department of
Children and Family Services, and
they had been involved before.
And what did they find?
It was unfounded.
There's no evidence of significant
abuse.
Do you think Heather was
manipulating adults into thinking that
her stepmother was evil?
I don't know if she
was intentionally manipulating adults, but
that was definitely what happened.
One thing's clear to investigators.
Heather was in someone else's
care in the two weeks
after she left that teacher's
house, during that critical time
when Bonnie went missing.
So now, of course, detectives
are curious, who was she
with?
And why is Heather protecting
them?
And then I went to
stay at a friend's house.
Okay, and who was that?
Just a friend.
I don't want to get
them in trouble.
So, just a friend.
They helped me, and they
knew the situation, so.
Well, you know, I have
to ask who it is.
She was very resistant to
talk at all about where
she had been, or what
she's been doing, and who
with.
They're not going to get
in trouble, are they?
Well, I don't know about
that.
They don't know nothing. They
don't like Bonnie.
I don't, I don't want
to know where Bonnie's at.
And as seasoned investigators, you
thought she's hiding something?
Yes, and we had to
push hard enough to get
that information.
They told me they didn't
know Bonnie was missing, and
I don't want to get
them in trouble.
Because it'll be all my
fault.
It didn't mean to cause
them trouble.
And I didn't know Bonnie
was going to go missing.
So now, another layer to
this mystery.
She was painting a pretty
ugly picture of her stepmother.
And might that have motivated
somebody to try to protect
her?
Sure.
Are they just good Samaritans,
or something else?
There's maybe more to this
than just taking care of
Heather.
The trail will lead detectives
down these winding roads into
truly uncharted territory.
We didn't see that coming
from a mile away.
Bonnie Woodward disappeared in Alton
June 25th at about 3
in the afternoon after getting
off work.
Her family members haven't seen
or heard from her since
that day.
Bonnie Woodward has been missing
for over a week.
Her boyfriend of seven years,
Gary Wilmerth, says he catches
glimpses of her in every
passing stranger.
There was times I could
be at a store, pass
somebody on the street.
Could be the color of
their hair.
I remember talking to her
grandbabies.
They said, are you going
to bring Grandma back?
You got a picture of
these little bitty girls looking
at me.
Where's Grandma?
I just thought in my
heart she was going to
come back.
And I wasn't taking no
for an answer.
She was coming back.