And investigators say they aren't
taking no for an answer
either.
Bonnie's now 18 -year -old
stepdaughter, Heather Woodward, who also
strangely went missing a week
before Bonnie, has now suddenly
reappeared.
Okay, Heather, we just need
to ask you a few
things here.
After hours of questioning from
detectives, Heather seems finally ready
to reveal the identity of
the people she says helped
her run away.
They're not going to get
in trouble, are they?
I don't know about that,
but I want to at
least know what, what, where
you've been.
I want to make sure
that you're safe.
Do they have any kids
your age?
Okay.
So is Nathan Carroll's family?
The police department had learned
that she had been at
the Carroll house.
Heather had told Roger Carroll
and Monica Carroll that she
had run away from home
because Bonnie was mean to
her, and that she had
gone to the Carroll house
to hide from Bonnie until
she turned 18.
Both Monica and Roger were
in the medical field, and
their son Nathan was a
typical 16 -year -old high
school student.
There was no criminal history
on record for them, no
police involvement, no arrests or
anything like that.
The Carrolls go to the
same church in Wood River,
so the Carrolls get to
know Heather, I think, on
church -related activities.
And one of those church
activities they went to?
A graduation party for Heather
and other seniors, just two
weeks before Bonnie went missing.
We obviously had to explore
the avenue of, are they
involved with Bonnie?
I think the police were
like, well, they had, you
know, Heather at the house,
then what else do they
know?
We went to their listed
address in the Jersey County
area.
They're living in among 60
acres of property.
It's just a lot of
wooded, open land.
What jumps out at you
about Roger Carroll?
He's in his 40s with
the brownish -gray hair, 5
'10 -ish.
His primary car is a
silver 2005 Chevrolet Malibu, which
is the suspect vehicle description.
We towed the vehicle to
our police department and ultimately
processed this vehicle for any
evidence related to our case.
This investigation is now shifting
into high gear.
Monica and Roger Carroll come
in for questioning.
You are Roger William Carroll,
Jr.
I don't want to answer
any more questions until we
speak with our attorney.
Okay.
You decided to be evoked
right to counsel, correct?
Yes, ma 'am.
Heather Woodward, Bonnie's stepdaughter, is
also called in again the
very same day
and pressed for more information
about the day Bonnie went
missing.
What do you know about
Bonnie leaving and what happened
whenever she left or was...
I mean, I know...
I know that she got
in the car with some
guy and they drove off,
that's all I know.
Did they talk about the
car?
Yeah, it was a silver
and gray car, Malibu.
Okay.
That's it. That's all I
know.
Does that sound like any
car that you're familiar with?
No.
Oh, besides Roger's car.
Okay.
Look, Roger wanted her to
fly.
Investigators then confront Heather with
a new piece of information.
They found out that she
and the Carrolls were together
at a lake house in
the days just before Bonnie
went missing.
Okay.
They went down to Monica's
parents in Goreville, Illinois on
a small trip, just the
four of them.
And detectives grow even more
suspicious when Heather shares that
Roger and his son Nathan
returned home by themselves on
the same day Bonnie disappeared.
Roger and Nathan came home
on Friday.
We came home on Saturday,
me and Monica.
Why did they leave on
Friday?
Monica told me that he
just wanted to get home
and he made Nathan go
with him.
He brought Nathan with him,
got up and left at
7 o 'clock in the
morning on June 5th.
On June 25th, Friday morning,
the day Bonnie disappeared.
Now, the question I have
here is, the guy that
meets with Bonnie up at
the nursing home, he's in
a gray Malibu, silver gray
Malibu.
How do I know that
Roger's not the one that
met with Bonnie up there
that Friday?
I don't know.
Roger, Bonnie's never met Roger,
so I don't know why
she came to the car
with him.
What if he told her,
hey, I know where Heather
is.
Why don't you come with
me?
And.
You need to pick her
up.
I don't.
Do you think Bonnie would
have gotten in a car
with him then?
No, she doesn't care about
me.
So you have a lot
of circumstantial evidence, but nothing
that cracks the case open.
It is all circumstantial.
There wasn't enough to link
Roger Carroll or Monica Carroll
to Bonnie's disappearance.
However, both of them at
that time were charged with
harboring a runaway.
Both Roger and Monica plead
not guilty to this charge,
but this turns out to
be a helpful tool for
investigators.
In getting those charges.
We can also get fingerprints.
We can get photographs.
And then you put Roger
in a lineup.
We did.
We used this mugshot primarily
with the employees at Unismith.
And that did not come
up with a match.
It did not.
That resulted in no positive
IDs.
The family members must be
chomping at the bit at
this point.
They are.
But sometimes the cases move
when they want to move.
Did you feel like there
had to have been somebody
out there that knew more
than they were saying?
I think.
I think that somebody that
is just trying to locate
a loved one often feels
like somebody's not talking or
somebody's lying.
Summer winds to a close
without Bonnie Woodward and without
answers until news of a
body found on the banks
of the Mississippi River here
in Alton, Illinois, leaves her
loved ones holding their breath.
Every time a body comes
up, we call 51 days
exactly.
She's been gone and we
have not one solid answer.
That body, it turns out,
is not Bonnie Woodward.
But.
But a break in the
case is coming.
The lab results from Bonnie's
abandoned truck are back.
And the results are stunning.
The crime lab comes back
with a very significant hit.
Yes.
You understand what we're trying
to tell you right now?
There's new physical evidence in
this case.
I said we have to
jump now.
This is our time.
I'm thinking I'm going to
die.
It's crazy.
Absolutely crazy.