Okay, we are recording.
I said, stop it. Just
stop doing this. Let me
go. Just let me go.
I'll do anything you want
me to do. Just let
me go.
Tonight, a third woman in
danger who broke the bizarre
mystery of a missing mother.
It didn't mean to cause
a problem. I didn't know
Bonnie was going to go
missing.
Who's been hiding daughter Heather?
And could Bonnie have ended
up in the same place?
Family members must be chomping
at the bit at this
point.
It was a needle in
a haystack. We had 60
acres of property. We didn't
know where to look, what
to look for.
Nathan, you can agree to
walk us through a few
areas that are of interest
in our investigation.
We got a hit on
the prints.
And on a scale of
1 to 10 of your
suspicion level, where did it
go?
Yeah, it's piped.
Any idea what they were?
Little pieces of white things,
but I don't know exactly
what it was.
The family's falling apart, and
we have to jump now.
This is our time.
She now is starting to
put...
Everything together and is fearing
for her own life at
the same time.
He said, I have killed
for you. I have killed
for you.
That sounds like bingo.
Summer has turned to fall
in Alton, Illinois.
48 -year -old mom and
nurse's aide, Bonnie Woodward, hasn't
been seen in over three
months.
That's an eternity in a
missing persons case.
We didn't know technically if
she was alive or dead
in the months that followed.
None of her family members
heard from her.
But the Illinois State Police...
The crime lab has been
busy processing evidence, including fingerprints
found on Bonnie's truck.
In September, prints come in.
Right. I got a phone
call from my evidence technician
who told me we got
a hit on the prints.
It's Roger Carroll's.
So Roger Carroll's fingerprints are
on this driver's door.
And on a scale of
1 to 10 of your
suspicion level, where did it
go?
Yeah, it's piped.
Roger Carroll is brought in
again for questioning.
While police...
As a notable cause, conduct
a massive search at the
Carroll's sprawling rural residence.
It was a needle in
a haystack. We had 60
acres of property.
We didn't know where to
look, what to look for.
Neighbors are stunned by the
police operation.
It's crazy. Absolutely crazy.
Couldn't believe it, the amount
of police that were coming
by.
And we had more than
60 police officers.
Multiple agencies.
We had a lot of
people. We had cadaver dogs.
And an airborne search.
And an airborne search, yes.
There's probably close to 30
firearms at this residence.
Multiple crates of ammunition were
also seen.
Oh, I thought they was
going to find a body
or something.
The cadaver dogs did alert
on certain areas of the
property.
But subsequent digs of those
areas revealed no results.
Meanwhile, this time in the
police interrogation room for a
second interview, Roger is more
chatty.
My mom, she's like, oh
my God, did you do
this?
Mom, no, I didn't do
it.
Roger tells investigators that he
invited Bonnie's daughter, Heather, to
stay with him and his
family.
Only after becoming concerned about
her account of a troubled
home life.
So then Heather calls you
guys?
Yes.
I could hear her crying.
She was just frantic, you
know.
Oh my God, Bonnie called
and said that she's going
to come get me tomorrow.
That I have to pack
my stuff up and I
don't know what I'm going
to do.
Right.
So, she kind of...
Played on your soft hearts
and said, can I come
stay there?
She never said, can I
come stay?
Just to be honest about
it, I'm the one who
said, hey, you know, this
is a bunch of crap.
Why don't we just go?
You know, she can stay
with us.
Okay, okay.
I'm the one that said
that.
As far as Bonnie, you've
never had a conversation with
that woman.
And you've never been face
to face with that woman.
You know where she lives,
but you've never, other than
you've driven by there.
Like two times, right?
Yes, that's correct.
And you've never been in
her vehicle.
Yeah.
And you've never had occasion
to handle her vehicle or
touch her vehicle.
That's correct.
But there's one little detail
investigators have been deliberately coy
about when talking to Roger
Carroll.
So finally, I was at
the end of the interview.
I was like, how do
we explain it that your
fingerprints are all over her
driver's door?
He stumbled just a bit
and says,
They've not been framed.
I mean, no, there's no
way that my fingerprints are
on that car door.
Or my DNA is on
that car door.
There just is no way.
He's asking, like, my prints
aren't on that door.
I'm like, well, yes, they
are.
I don't see how.
There's no way my fingerprints
are all over the door
of that car.
They are.
So he denied it still.
And the interview terminated pretty
quick after that.
Not only were his fingerprints
found on her car,
but he denied ever having
met her or ever been
there and ever been in
that parking lot.
So what do you make
of that?
That he's lying.
There's a third interview with
Heather.
Heather stays firm during this
interview that she didn't have
anything to do with it.
Bonnie went missing around 2
to 3 o 'clock in
the afternoon.
And his prints are on
Bonnie's truck.
What do you think?
I never wanted that to
happen to Bonnie.
I mean, sometimes I, you
know, she's mean, but I
wouldn't do that to her.
I didn't tell him to
touch Bonnie.
She was the only thing
I knew.
I wouldn't hurt her.
The police process.
Rogers graced at Anne.
But here's the thing.
They don't find any fibers
or DNA belonging to Bonnie
or even her fingerprints.
And they don't come up
with much of the Carroll
house either.
After the search in September,
there was really no evidence
found at the residence that
100 % put Bonnie there
at the Carroll property.
When you take somebody to
trial for first degree murder,
you better be right and
you better be ready because
you only get one shot.
We still didn't have Bonnie's
remains.
We didn't know if Bonnie
was alive or dead.
We didn't know if she
was dead at that time.
And what we did know
is that Roger Carroll was
lying.
Roger Carroll, based on the
lies that he told, was
charged with the offense of
obstruction.
Family members and friends felt
that he needed to be
charged with murder.
But based on it only
being a circumstantial case at
this point, that would have
been quite a stretch for
us.
So the case goes cold.
Your aunt is still missing.
What was that like for
your family?
I know that it was
very hard emotionally for many
family members.
It would take eight years
and one newly installed prosecutor
combing through a pile of
Madison County cold cases
And the first one you
stumbled on was Bonnie Woodward.
First one, Bonnie Woodward.
to breathe life back into
Bonnie Woodward's investigation.
Jennifer Mudge decides to try
to open a cold case,
but even before you can
relaunch anything, you get a
startling phone call.
We got a call from
Roger Carroll's neighbor and he's
asking me,
he's like, do you know
what's going on at the
Carroll's house?
I said, God, Roger, stop
it.
Just stop doing this.
Let me go.
Just let me go.
I'll do anything you want
me to do.
Just let me go.