I'm fighting. I'm fighting with
everything that's within me.
What are you thinking at
the time?
What am I thinking? I'm
thinking I'm going to die.
Roger Carroll had been charged
with obstruction of justice in
the disappearance of Bonnie Woodward.
But now, eight years later,
he's being accused of something
else altogether.
By, of all people, his
wife of over 30 years,
Monica.
In March of 2018, we
received information from the Jersey
County Sheriff's Department
that there was a domestic
situation in which Roger had
caused injury to Monica.
I didn't know his connection.
I didn't know this was
the Bonnie Woodward suspect.
So I went the next
day and met her several
hours from here where she
was kind of hyped out.
Okay, we are recording.
He told me I was
fat, disgusting, so fat and
disgusting that nobody would want
to have anything to do
with me.
The first thing you notice?
The first thing you notice
on the dash cam is
A, the injuries to her
face, and B, beyond the
injuries, just the fear.
She said for the most
part it was a good
marriage until there was some
infidelity like a few years
prior.
She had recently figured out
more infidelity and then had
filed for divorce.
He was really withdrawn after
serving with the divorce papers.
I thought he would be
happy because just a couple
weeks before he said, I
want a divorce.
They had separate bedrooms.
But while she slept in
her bedroom, she not only
locked the door, but she
put a dresser up against
the door because she was
scared.
Monica tells Detective Nick Manns
about the alleged attack in
which, as she's getting ready
for work,
she says Roger corners her
in the laundry room.
Roger is looking out the
garage door, like making sure
Nathan has left.
And he turned and he
acted like he was going
to have normal conversation.
And he reached over to
the back of the car.
He was looking at me
from the back of my
head, grabbed my hair, and
jerked me and then dragging
me around by my hair
with his right hand, he
was hitting me in the
head with the taser gun.
And how do you know
it was a taser gun?
What was it doing?
Because it shocked me.
So he drags it up
your neck?
He drags it up my
neck.
He looked shocked.
And I was screaming, Roger,
don't do this. Roger, don't
do this.
I started screaming, Nathan, Nathan.
Screaming for Nathan as hard
as I could.
Screaming for help.
Nathan, unfortunately, had already left
early for work.
So then I knew all
my help was gone.
And I remember when he
hit me up here. He
hit me and drug.
And the shocked look on
his face.
I said, God, Roger, stop
it. Just stop doing this.
Let me go. Just let
me go. I'll do anything
you want me to do.
Just let me go.
And he had this shocked
look on his face.
It's like he was surprised
that I was still talking.
Monica says she somehow manages
to get a hold of
the taser and throws it
into the next room.
You still have some abrasion,
some little swelling there.
I had blood. Pretty much
every place that these things
are, I had blood smeared.
All these red marks are
from your fight with him.
These are from him.
During this time, Monica does
what so many victims unfortunately
have to do, but it's
a survival thing.
How am I going to
get out of this situation?
And she starts to deescalate
it slowly, verbally deescalate the
situation.
I was just thinking, don't
get him agitated. Talk him
down.
And I said, Roger, you've
been a good dad.
You were a good husband.
But you're not the man.
He said that I married
30 years ago.
And he'd said it before.
He said, I know.
I'm not that same person.
He said, I am a
monster.
He said, I have so
much anger and hate in
me.
And I can't control it
no more.
He said, at times, I
feel like I have the
devil living inside me.
Eventually, that got to the
point where he allowed her
to get up and get
ready for work and go.
As soon as I got
in my car, I hit
the lock button.
Put it in reverse.
And took out.
Then she provided us information
that she knew him to
possess firearms.
And she believed him to
be suicidal at the time.
He says, I've been thinking
about just going out into
the woods and never coming
back.
Detective Mann says he went
to search for Roger the
morning of the alleged attack.
We believe he's a danger,
obviously, to her and to
our community, but also to
himself.
So I'm driving down this
road.
Which is Creek Road, which
is where he lives.
And this is actually, that
would be his house at
the time.
He and Monica lived there.
That was their home.
I keep going up this
hill.
You can see it's pretty
rugged terrain.
I don't even realize at
that time that this is
his property.
So I go up here.
And I go left.
And I drive across this
field.
And I get out of
my car.
And when I get up
along this trail, I see
something down there.
And I keep moving closer.
And it's...
It's him.
Roger was lethargic.
I felled in his jacket
pocket, which turned out to
be a bag of needles,
of syringes.
Then I found a vial
of what I knew to
be insulin.
I asked him if he
was diabetic.
And he said no, that
he had hurt his wife
and that he was trying
to kill himself.
I called my dispatch and
said, send an ambulance this
way.
What's the ambulance?
No, this guy's not diabetic.
He's with insulin.
Attention, Brighton Road.
Rescue in Creek Road for
52 -year -old male.
Took an overdose of insulin.
The suicide attempt.
But what Detective Mann soon
learns is that his fellow
investigator, Scott Golicki,
has been looking at Roger
Carroll as Bonnie Woodward's possible
killer.
Immediately, Scott and I said,
the family's falling apart.
And we have to jump
now.
This is our time.
Because at that point, you
double down on every member
of the Carroll family.
Right.
We need a talker.
They need a talker.
And they're about to get
one.
And investigators get a story
they had not prepared for.