Newly installed prosecutor Jennifer Mudge
is working hard with police
to try to solve
Bonnie Woodward's cold case. They
believe they can break it
if a Carroll family member
talks.
As detectives are talking to
Roger Carroll's wife, Monica, they
get intriguing new info.
She remembers her husband taking
a peculiar interest in Bonnie
Woodward's daily life
before she disappeared. Monica talked
about conversations that she thought
was odd about
where specifically Bonnie worked, what
type of work schedule she
had. I don't remember what
shift she worked or you
know the days but I
remember those were in conversation.
I just
remember thinking that it was
very odd that he's asking
all these details. She now
is starting to
put everything together and is
fearing for her own life
at the same time. Looking
back on it now
I've been scared for a
long time but I just
I wasn't
you know I didn't know
what to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do. I didn't know what
to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do. I didn't know what
to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do. I didn't know what
to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do. I didn't know what
to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do. I didn't know what
to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do. I didn't know what
to do. I didn't know
what to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do. I didn't know what
to do. I didn't know
what to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do. I didn't know what
to do. I didn't know
what to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do. I didn't know what
to do. I didn't know
what to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do. I didn't know what
to do. I didn't know
what to do. I didn't
know what to do. I
didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what to
do.
You know, I had to
say a word, but if
you want to hear me
out, I think it might
be worth your while, but
it's your prerogative. You're driving
this bus.
I had started it with,
hey, Roger, you don't have
to say anything if you
don't want, but we've opened
this case. This train's coming
down the road.
I think what's going to
happen now is that this
is a homicide investigation, and
it's moving in that direction.
I was basically telling him,
charges on this case are
now imminent.
But some of the intimate
details and the specific details,
only you know.
It's the right thing to
do for Bonnie yourself, also
the right thing for you.
There's no way you're enjoying
living with this.
But if Detective Golicki is
counting on a crisis of
conscience from Roger Carroll, he's
about to be disappointed.
We've opened this case. This
train's coming down the road.
Like, I'm giving you an
opportunity to try to mitigate
the circumstances.
Are you comfortable with the
whole situation?
Well, no. I mean, I'm
not going to talk to
you. You know, call my
attorney, please.
Like, I interviewed him for
an hour and some change,
and really for 55 minutes,
he just didn't speak.
Since Roger completely clams up,
they bring his wife Monica
in again. And turns out,
she does have more to
share.
So you had a feeling
that something...
Something went right?
Something happened.
Otherwise, you, I think...
You would have questioned it.
Your internal feelings.
Said that something went right.
Yeah.
That things weren't right.
When he said that he's
killed people for me, to
protect me and Nathan, I
know that's not right.
I know it's not right
that he should kill someone,
feel that he has a
right to kill someone to
protect me.
And you're not aware of
anything else in your history
with Roger or...
You know, with Nathan, that
he would be talking about
other than Bonnie Woodward.
Right.
The only person that come
to my mind would be
Bonnie.
Monica says Roger issues her
a stark warning about Bonnie's
family.
He made it sound like
it'd be my fault if
something happened to our family,
if I ever told him.
So I didn't want to
be the one to be
the cause of our family
being torn apart.
I didn't want to hear
it.
Because I recall I told
him I didn't want to
hear it.
We knew that Monica was
not there at that time.
And we were also pretty
confident that she didn't show
up until a day later.
That's when Monica describes approaching
their son Nathan with her
suspicions.
I told Nathan that Roger
told me, I have killed
for you.
And he was like, don't
ever repeat that, Mom.
Don't ever repeat.
But what might it take
for Nathan to start talking?