I wasn't to the point
to admit it yet.
But the really chilling words
about Roger, that was still
to come.
He said, I have killed
for you.
I have hurt a lot
of people.
But I killed for you,
and I think that's mine.
Meanwhile, Roger is released from
the hospital after his insulin
overdose
and is brought directly into
police custody.
Where Detective Golicky greets him
again after eight long years.
Roger, what are you doing?
What's going on?
Remember me?
Scott Golicky.
So after all that, you
sit down with Roger years
later from the last interrogation.
Yes.
Is he a different man?
Yes, we both aged a
lot, probably me more than
him.
After the domestic, he was
clearly suicidal.
And so when I see
him, it's not his best
day.
It's not his best day.