Investigators are drilling down on
the Carroll family,
and the story of what
they think might have happened
to Bonnie Woodward is beginning
to take shape.
Monica, she's not present. She's
not a co -defendant on
the incident.
I honestly do believe that
he did away with Bonnie
Woodward.
I don't know how, but
I don't know how.
We doubled down on the
theory that Nathan was likely
with Roger at the time
that Bonnie disappeared.
Nathan was 16 years old
at the time that this
crime was committed.
Nathan is now 24.
You're talking about a kid
versus an adult, so I
think maybe you focus on
him.
We made several attempts to
talk to Nathan, and he
refused to talk to law
enforcement.
We served him with a
subpoena to come testify in
front of the grand jury.
I made a decision to
grant him immunity at the
time.
If he would tell us
the full truth, and then
fate sort of took over
from there.
What did he say that
tipped his hand to you
that he was about to
spill the whole truth?
He held up the immunity
paper and said, this is
good no matter what I
tell you, and I said
yes.
He put his hands on
the rail, and boy, that
testimony was gripping.
He broke down, and he
started crying, and he said
he was going to tell
us everything.
That's kind of a thing
maybe you see on TV
with people breaking down in
the courtroom and spilling the
beans in the courtroom, but
it really never happens, but
it did.
Sitting in the room was
12 grand jurors, myself and
Jennifer, and Nathan's attorney.
It was absolute silence. You
could hear the clock tick.
It's like watching the weight
of the world being lifted
off this young man's shoulders.
He told the entire story
about what happened that day.
He says that he's on
vacation.
With his whole family, they
have Heather there, and his
dad said to him the
night before, you and I
are leaving early tomorrow.
They drove to Eunice Smith
Nursing Home, and his dad
said, good, she's at work.
Then after they get home,
Roger changed clothes, clipped his
fingernails, he shaved, and retrieved
his Stoger 9mm from the
house, and left Nathan there
by himself.
He told Nathan he was
going to get Bonnie.
Nathan set up a tent
in the backyard.
The tent in the backyard
was essentially a death trap
to lure Bonnie to the
backyard and not into the
residence.
He's eating lunch. Next thing
he hears is eight or
nine gunshots, and they're close.
They're in his driveway.
He walks outside, and that's
when he sees feet with
tennis shoes on and tan
scrubs.
There are a few things
that stay with me.
Like, he remembers that he
was in a car accident.
He was eating leftover deli
meat sandwiches from Heather's graduation
party.
If you're making a story
up, you don't go that
detailed into what kind of
lunch you're having.
But the next detail may
be the most disturbing of
all.
Nathan tells the grand jury
that his dad had him
light a fire in the
backyard,
and testifies he watched as
his father loaded Bonnie's body
into a bucket loader,
a tractor with a scoop
on the front of it,
and bring her to that
burn pit.
And they start a massive
fire.
It had to be stoked.
All day, all night, every
couple of hours.
And Roger had Nathan help
him do that.
When you heard the scope
of what he confessed to,
what went through your mind?
I don't think we thought
fire or burned on a
brush pile.
Talk about being haunted.
Right. Like, not only is
Roger creating a horrible thing
for him to live with,
it seems like he created
a horrible thing for his
son to live with.
After his grand jury testimony,
Nathan brings investigators back to
the house.
What you're about to see
is the actual video police
captured
as Nathan brings them back
to where he says the
crime took place,
a spot first identified eight
years earlier by cadaver dogs.
During our search in September
of 2010, we had 60
acres that we had to
worry about.
Now we have a few
hundred feet.
Nathan, you've agreed to just
walk us through a few
areas that are of interest
in our investigation involving your
father,
and the investigation of missing
person Bonnie Woodward.
Nathan points out the back
corner of the residence where
he found Bonnie's body
and saw her, where the
shot had come from.
This is where she laid.
I never saw the full
body. I was over there.
Okay.
And I saw feet.
It was in that site
that we did find a
nine millimeter cartridge,
which was significant because Nathan
had identified that Roger had
used a nine millimeter handgun.
Ultimately that day in shooting
Bonnie.
The second site that Nathan
took law enforcement to was
what we refer to as
the burn pit.
Followed by the creek where
Nathan says he saw his
dad dump Bonnie's ashes.
So we had a site
number three for where this
was dumped into the creek
bed.
Was that tractor with the
bucket end on it?
Correct.
Little pieces of white things,
but I don't know exactly
what it was.
They don't know any idea
what they were?
I guess it would be
bone, but I don't know.
Law enforcement were able to
find 27 pieces of what
they believed to be bone
fragment
that were collected and sent
off to the lab to
see if any DNA or
any connection could be made
to Bonnie.
All right, gentlemen. Thank you.
Based on the version of
events that Nathan gave,
we felt comfortable charging Roger
Carroll with first degree murder
of Bonnie Woodward.
A man linked in 2010
to the disappearance of Bonnie
Woodward today has been charged
with her murder.
I thought, wow.
I mean, they're actually charging
somebody for murder.
But not so fast.
Some critical evidence will be
unveiled in court which could
upend the case.
The DNA on those bone
fragments?
It's not what police expected.