Matt, what time did you
get here today?
9 .30 -ish.
All right.
So, me and Emily are
just hanging out.
I'm shaking.
Vito comes in, and he's
got the gun that I've
got set out on the
counter.
I just had it sitting
there.
What did you have it
sitting there for?
I was going to talk
to Emily about the importance
of, hey, you know, for
one, this dude really liked
you.
For two, he talked about
creepy stuff.
And for three, he came
to the house.
Was it your gun or
your father's gun?
It's my dad's gun.
All right.
And he walks around the
corner, and he says, you
know, that if I do
anything, he's going to shoot
Emily.
And then he goes in,
you know, he tapes this
up.
He wasn't trying to break
anything or steal anything.
He just wanted to talk
to Emily.
Did he have the gun
in his hand?
And every time, the whole
time he was talking?
Yes.
That's when mom and dad
came home.
He ran outside.
Me and Emily trying to
get free.
And that's when we heard
the first gunshot.
Still at that point, I
thought he had fired off
a shot to scare somebody.
And then I heard a
second one in a different
place.
Before I could think, he
runs back inside, doesn't say
a word, and shoots Emily.
He's out of bullets.
He reloads.
And I made my move.
I pushed him back up
against the wall.
As soon as he broke
away, bam.
It was just that quick.