You know, we towed Vito's
vehicle post, okay, and we
searched it, and we found
the very same
shell casings that we found
at your house in the
back of his vehicle, spent.
We sent those off,
we had them tested against
the gun, and the shell
casings we found in the
cup holder in the back
seat of Vito's Explorer were
fired from the gun you
had in your possession that
day. And we can't
figure that out, man. We're
stuck. And that was the
ruse, because we were really
confident that
that they were going to
match. We had a working
theory that they planned the
murders at the
Waffle House, and Ryan gave
Vito a handgun to go
do some target shooting. We
don't understand how
that's the case. Could he
have stolen my gun out
of my truck? You tell
us. You know, you said
you
never lost it anyway, so
that didn't happen. It wasn't
lost. Well, I mean, did
y 'all go target
practice?
No. Okay. Now, that's a
speed bump. We're just going
to have to figure out
what happened there,
why he has used your
gun to shoot stuff. He
must have taken it out
of my truck. When? How?
I don't
know. You could see the
wheels start turning in his
head. He didn't know they
were in that truck.
If he did, he forgot
about it. And then he
had to come up with
some other way that that
happened.
Okay.
What about Waffle House?
Waffle House.
You ever been to Waffle
House with him?
Let me think. Yes, one
night with him and Ann.
Why'd you leave that out?
Well, it's just, I don't
remember that. That's a petty
detail.
Ryan, that's Vito we're talking
about. All right. That's the
guy that killed him.
The guy you told me
on Sunday we met one
time.
I know, but that was
before. That was when he
was just a layabout presence.
It's just you and her
and him. It's not a
layabout presence.
It seems like they were
doing a lot of talking
at the table.
Y 'all were chatting it
up. Chatty Cathy, man.
Well, that's kind of what
I do.
Look, I remember, you know,
it took you saying it
to jog my memory that
I even went to Waffle
House.
You left out being with
the guy that killed your
entire family.
But I didn't, how could
I have known that at
the time?
It's possible you gave him
the gun to kill your
family.
No.
That's not possible.
And how did his shell
casings get in his truck?
That's...
I don't know.
Well, I think I do.
I think I do, too.
We've been waiting for you
to tell the truth here.
All you're doing is walking
in circles. You're dancing in
a circle here.
Okay? Man up.
Look, the only thing I
can think of is he
might have stolen it.
Even while he must have
stolen it.
Do you think anybody with
half a brain is going
to think that he stole
it and brought it back?
Maybe.
No, they're not, Ryan.
You're in a quandary.
This looks bad, because it
is bad.
Your whole family's dead and
you're alive, Ryan.
You got out of there
without a mark.
Listen to me. Don't talk.
The gun that was used
to kill your family was
given to Vito by you
for whatever reason.
I don't know if it
was for money or what,
but you gave Vito that
gun to come and assassinate
your family.
Okay?
They didn't deserve that.
And you can only make
that right...
...by being honest.
All I ever did was
try to help that kid.
The evidence doesn't suggest it.
I did that all the
time. That's what I do.
I help out. I bring
food.
Ryan, listen to me. Listen
to me.
You didn't help your mom,
your dad, and your sister.
There's a reason I have
that reputation. My dad was
the same way. He'd help
anybody.
Your dad's dead because of
you, Ryan.
My dad is not dead
because of me.
Yes, he is.
No, you can't be serious
right now. You can't be
serious.
Let's get down to the
nitty -gritty.
The duct tape was so
minimal on me.
It was so minimal on
you and so maximal on
your sister. It made no
sense.
And your story today didn't
make any sense.
Listen, it's not believable.
It's not believable.
The only guy that survives
is you.
Your sister was shot three
times.
Your mom and dad are
dead.
The guy that, in my
opinion, you brought in there
to do all this stuff,
you killed.
I believe that happened.
Ryan, listen to me. Do
you see how this looks?
Do you hear where this
is going?
And then, yeah.
Can I go out and
smoke, please?
While y 'all have a
minute?
You're going to come back
about the fruit.
I have to give him
some contact information.
While we were outside, he
had that for Ernie.
Guys, look.
Y 'all have both been
decent and fair with me
throughout this whole process.
I think up until tonight.
And I know this isn't
a requirement for the job.
But one thing it definitely
wasn't was nice.
Or, you know, it was
not courtesy.
I understand that, Ryan.
But killing your family ain't
nice either, brother.
You know, and I've got
a job to do.
And so I don't really
care if he thinks I'm
nice or not.
You know, I want to
get to the bottom of
what happened.
You've got test results to
come in.
And what you're basing these
opinions on is something that
nobody can know.
What he was thinking, what
he was knowing.
Based on evidence.
And...
I mean, just put simply,
if y 'all have this...
Let me just have a
minute with Detective Miller.
I'll be back in a
minute.
That's for your lawyer.
I'm not asking you any
questions.
Okay.