Where did she go? Right
here? She goes right here.
She goes right here. He
gets her down. He gets
her down. She goes down.
And he just kind of
like straddles her. Emily's like
kicking around and everything. Squirming.
I mean, not actually like
fighting, fighting, but she's really
resisting trying to get out.
And she's squirming and she
kind of works herself where
she's kind of like wedged
inside of this doorway. And
he's just straddling, riding.
Riding. This is one of
those times where I just
wonder if I run over.
It looked more like acting
than emotion. My personal opinion
and the opinion of family
is that Emily would have
kicked Vito's tail, even if
he had a gun.
I think it took both
of them to get her
corralled and get her taped
up because I think she
would have fought tooth and
nail.
Once I got the gun
away from you, I mean,
we're still locked up like
this. He has started to
grab me with that hand,
so you haven't got me
grabbed.
As he's trying to demonstrate
here how he got it
away from him, he just
can't make it work. And
he's kind of laughing.
I think he thinks, and
I've tried to show them
what happened.
And this isn't working. It
is a, I'm in trouble
after.
So we made a trip
to Waffle House. We're getting
the video ready.
And we found the date
and time roughly, and we
started looking and all of
a sudden we see these
people come walking through the
door.
And there's Ann. And there's
Ryan and there's Vito.
And they walked over to
a booth. That was on
the 21st of October.
And Ryan, in all of
his interviews so far,
said he had only met
Vito on the 23rd.
So he's obviously deliberately lied
to us about how long
he had known Vito.
Things were adding up. But
in order to arrest someone
on a felony offense, you
need probable cause.
In a perfect world, we
wanted a confession.
Have I done an okay
job? I'm not the best
explainer in the world. I
never have been.
Every time we talked to
him up to that point,
it was very casual, really
not questioning him on anything.
And this time, we wanted
to start kind of putting
pressure on him.
And looking at the case
out there, there's a lot
of things that have popped
up in our investigation that
we want to iron out.
Of course.
Alright. The whole gun thing.
First, you told me that
you went to the basement
and retrieved the gun. Because
we went over it. Could
you get it out of
the state?
I actually said that I
retrieved it.
Yes, you went down to
the basement to get it.
We talked about it for
a while. And then today,
you told me you brought
it.
The gun being in your
car versus downstairs in the
basement in your dad's gun
room, I'll call it?
Correct.
Okay. That's an inconsistency that
popped up today.
Correct. Well, the thing is,
I did a bad job
of explaining.
That's not a bad job
of explaining. It's totally the
opposite.
I thought, no, your communication
skills are fine. You just
happened to have killed your
family.
And you don't want to
tell us what happened.
Let's go on to the
next one. This one is
what I'm curious about.
Okay.
The duct tape. We've seen
it today on the reenactment.
Yeah. Bet y 'all could
get it.
Yeah. It wasn't that hard.
Yeah. And the thing is,
I suppose I could have
too, but it just wasn't,
I wasn't, I wasn't thinking
that.
Okay. You know, he's paying
a lot of attention to
your sister.
Mm -hmm.
And you could have just
ran out the side door.
Why?
Why didn't you do that
and go for help?
No way.
Why?
Well, my sister's there.
Did you love your sister?
Yes.
Did it cross your mind
at all you wanted to
just rip his head off
and piss down his throat
for doing that to your
sister?
Yes. And that's what made
it, that's what made that
so difficult.
But if I had run
at him from across the
room and failed, you know,
your cards played.
Why play your only card
when you can't be sure
it'll work?
Because if you don't, you're
probably going to die anyway.